新年倒计时正在进行中
The countdown
to the New Year is on.
点燃那些烤架并冰镇香槟
Fire up those
grills and ice the Cristal,
因为今年是时候出去参加派对了
'cause it is time to party
this year out the door
并欢迎新人的到来
and welcome the new one
right in.
我真的很兴奋
I'm really excited.
我认为这将是非常好的一年
I think it's gonna be
a really good year.
当然市中心会有
Of course, there's gonna be
一场盛大的派对随着烟花
one big party downtown
as fireworks light up
照亮港口上空的夜空
the night sky
over the Inner Harbor.
安全再次
And safety, once again,
成为重中之重
it's a top priority.
全国各地的警察部门...
All across the country,
police departments...
午夜钟声过后
Coming after
the stroke of midnight,
我们将举办一场盛大的派对
we have quite a party in store.
暴风雨前有一种相对的平静
It's a relative calm
before the storm.
我想告诉你它在我身后的样子
I want to show you
what it looks like behind me.
我们用五彩纸屑做过测试
We've tested the confetti.
我们还测试了烟花
We've tested the fireworks.
相信我 你不仅会看到它们
Believe me,
you're not just gonna see them.
你会感觉到它们...在你的胸口
You're gonna feel them--
in your chest.
是的！
- Yeah!
♪ 带上他们 我们打牌 ♪
♪ Bring 'em all round,
we'll play cards ♪
♪ 想知道你是否会打动我的心 ♪
♪ Wondering if you'll
strike my heart ♪
♪ 我们会搬到地板上
♪ We'll move to the floor
♪ 我会接受我的暗示
- ♪ And I'll take my cue
♪ 但是 宝贝  去做吧！ 做吧！
- ♪ But, baby
-  Do it! Do it!
做吧！ 做吧！ 做吧！
Do it! Do it! Do it!
♪ 我厌倦了玩你的游戏 ♪
♪ I'm sick and tired
of playing your games ♪
♪ 已经太晚了 我不会等... ♪
♪ It's too late,
I won't wait... ♪
♪ 太晚了 我不会等了
♪ It's too late, I won't wait
♪ 嘟 嘟 嘟嘟嘟
♪ Doo, doo, doo-doo-doo
♪ 嘟 嘟 嘟 嘟嘟嘟
♪ Doo, doo, doo, doo-doo-doo.
好的 有什么问题吗？
Okay, so what's the problem?
她就是问题所在
She's the problem.
好吗？ 这个女人
Okay? This woman is
让我的客户感到压力
- distressing my customers,
她拒绝离开
and she's refusing to leave.
嘿 就是这样
- Hey, that's it.
准备好了  我们走吧
You're done. Let's go.
别碰我 你这个小混蛋
Don't touch me,
you little shit.
你听到了吗？ 你好 哥们儿
- You hear that?
Hey, dude.
你是那个给顾客带来压力的人
You're the one
distressing the customers.
这位女士支付了她的餐费
The lady paid for her meal.
她有权吃完
She's entitled to finish it.
这是新年 伙计
It's New Year's, man.
是的 我知道这是新年
Yeah, I know it's New Year's.
我在这里工作 伙计
I'm working here, buddy.
好的
Great.
女士 这里不能带酒
Ma'am, you can't
bring alcohol in here.
尝试在没有它的情况下吃这种食物
Try eating this food
without it.
谢谢
Thank you.
看 她显然有问题
Look, she clearly
has a problem.
你为什么不让她说完就走？
Why don't you let her
just finish and leave?
因为她已经在这里呆了三个该死的小时 好吗？
Because she has been here
for three goddamn hours, okay?
嘿 听着 我不是想成为
Hey, listen,
I'm not trying to be
一个混蛋 但我需要那张桌子
an asshole,
but I need that table.
真的吗？  是的 真的
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
我需要那张桌子 我希望她离开 所以你的工作也是如此
I need that table, and I want
her gone, so do your job.
G25 代码 3
G25, Code 3.
所有处理非关键任务的单位
All units handling
noncritical tasks,
立即向霍普金斯广场报告
report to Hopkins Plaza immediately.
我重复一遍：G25 代码 3
- I repeat: G25, Code 3.
什么是G25？
What's a G25?
她留下来了
She stays.
主动射手
Active shooter.
25 名受害者报告  17人确认死亡
25 victims reported,
17 confirmed dead.
我们有报告称港口发生枪击事件
We got reports of
a shooter down at the harbor.
有人看到了什么吗？ 请确认
Any eyes? Please confirm.
6 区 地面控制 请进
Sector 6,
ground control, come in.
西费耶特街 305 号
OFFICER 3 [over radio]:
305 West Fayette Street,
公寓9B
apartment 9B.
死去的十几岁男孩 乔纳·米勒
Dead teenage boy, Jonah Miller.
弹道学需要立即清理房间
CST needs the room clear
right away.
我不能看着你死
WOMAN [sobbing]:
I can't watch you die.
我不能看着你死
305 西费耶特1409
OFFICER [over radio]:
305 West Fayette, 1409.
你能确认受害者已经死亡吗？
Can you confirm
victim deceased?
米勒夫人 我需要你把他放下
Mrs. Miller, I'm gonna
need you to lay him down.
对不起 我只是在做我的工作
I'm sorry,
I'm just doing my job.
你的工作是让他活着
Your job was to keep him alive.
所有居民
OFFICER [over speaker]:
All residents,
关掉你的灯
- switch off your lights.
远离窗户
Stay away from the windows.
不要离开你的建筑物
Do not leave your building.
这不是演习
This is not a drill.
所有居民 关灯
All residents,
switch off your lights.
你好
Hi.
我叫埃莉诺
My name's Eleanor.
你的是什么？  海莉
- What's yours?
- Haley.
米勒夫人？
Mrs. Miller?
你的女儿需要你  现在
Your daughter needs you. Now.
请让我带你们去你们的房间
Please let me take both of you
to your room.
一颗子弹通过
Single bullet through
朝北的窗户刺破了受害者的头部
north-facing window
punctured the victim's head,
然后以...的向下轨迹撞墙
then hit the wall
at a downward trajectory of...
...23 度
...23 degrees.
待命  各单位准备好了吗？
OFFICER [over radio]:
Stand by. All units ready?
你想失明吗？
Do you want to go blind?
屋顶狙击手 待命
OFFICER [over radio]:
Rooftop sniper, stand by.
任何更多的镜头 如果我们的人在移动 请告诉我
Any more shots, let me know
if our guy's on the move.
好的 好的  我们知道了
OFFICER [over radio]:
Okay, okay. We've got it.
红木街 12 号 17 楼
12 Redwood Street, 17th floor.
天哪他妈的
Jesus fuck.
这是 Heli 2 前往红杉
This is Heli 2,
heading to Redwood.
清除所有民用工艺品
Clear all civilian craft.
大家出去！ 出去！
Everybody, get out! Get out!
将自己从建筑物中移开！ 这边走！
Remove yourself from
the building! This way!
对 那是对的  嘿！ 停下！
- Yes, that's correct.
Hey! Stop!
不要离开前院   什么 你疯了吗？
- Do not leave the forecourt.
- What, are you insane?
这个地方着火了  带他们离开这里！
The place is on fire.
Get 'em out!
如果其中之一是射手怎么办？
What if one of them
is the shooter?
如果你们准备炸毁这个地方怎么办？
What if he's got
the whole place rigged to blow?
立即疏散他们！
Get 'em out now!
开始录制
Start recording.
什么？  获取视频中的每一张脸
- What?
- Get every face on video.
记录所有的面孔
Record. Every face.
在手机上获取它们
Get 'em on your phone.
快点！ 快点！
Let's go! Let's go!
进来！
Move in!
出去！ 马上离开大楼！
Out! Out of the building now!
走 走！
Go, go!
继续拍摄
Keep filming.
移动  快 快！
- Move it, move it, move it!
我有光！ 我有光！
I got light! I got light!
来吧 亲爱的
- Come on, honey.
穿过门 上楼梯
Through the door,
top of the stairs.
安全！
Clear!
All clear!
这间公寓很干净！
This apartment's clear!
没有人死在这里  连一根手指都没有
Nobody died here.
Not even a finger.
这就对了
That's it.
你没事
You're okay.
是的 你还好吗？
Yeah, you're all right?
帮我拿着这个  这里！
Hold this for me. Here!
嘿   嘿
Hey.
- Hey.
她没事  她只是晕过去了
She's all right.
She just fainted.
好的  -有时我确实有那种效果
Okay. -Sometimes I do
have that effect.
我要换你的面具 好吗？
I'm gonna swap
your mask, all right?
我很好  谢谢
I'm good. Thank you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我晕倒了多久？
How long was I out?
哎呀！  哦 哦 等等...
- Whoop!
- Oh, oh, hold...
我还好    你不会走下十七层楼梯
I'm okay. -You're not going
down 17 flights of stairs.
让我们把她弄走   是的
- Let's get her away.
- Yep.
好的  把她放下
Okay. Put her down.
好的  好 好 好 好
Okay, good.
Good, good, good, good.
慢慢的   好吧 跟着我的手指
- Easy.
- All right, follow my finger.
这就对了
That's it.
好的  好的
Okay. Good.
三项检查完成 长官 长官  不是一个迹象
Three full sweeps, sir.
Not a sign.
停车场、储藏室、电梯
Parking lot,
storage units, elevators.
是的 我们都知道建筑物是由什么构成的 指挥官
Yeah, we all know what a
building is made of, Commander.
不要再想 “我哪里没看过？”
Stop thinking,
"Where haven't I looked?"
嘿
- Hey.
开始思考 “我会躲在哪里？”
Start thinking,
"Where would I hide?"
给我你的手臂
Give me your arm.
麦克
Mac.
你有什么？  业主是挪威人
- What you got?
- The owner's Norwegian.
财务顾问   嗯
- Financial advisor.
- Uh-huh.
现在他在奥斯陆
He's in Oslo as we speak.
说他从来没有看过公寓
Says he never laid eyes
on the condo.
他得到它作为偿还债务
He got it as a debt repayment.
从那以后他就一直想卖掉它
He's been trying
to sell it ever since.
祝你好运   是的
- Good luck with that.
- Yeah.
妈的！ 他妈的！
- Oh, shit! Fuck!
对不起 伙计们  那些是预编程的
MAN [over radio]: Sorry, guys.
Those were preprogrammed.
我们正在禁用其他人
We're getting the others
shut off.
啊 他妈的
Ah, fuck.
确认那些是预编程的
MAN [over radio]: Confirming
those were preprogrammed.
确保将它们全部禁用
Make sure
you turn them all off.
我真的以为他们在向我们开枪
I seriously...
I thought we were getting shot.
伙计们 我们应该马上把那个厕所弄出来
Guys, we should get
that toilet right now.
在它被进一步污染之前
Before it gets contaminated
any further.
不 伙计们  所有的
No, guys. All of it.
全部...把它拉出来
The whole thing-- pull it out.
保持呼吸 好吗？ 抱歉
Keep breathing,
all right? -Excuse me.
通过你的鼻子  女士
- Through your nose.
Ma'am.
你觉得这个地方像急诊室吗？
Does this place look
like an ER to you?
是的  不
Right.
No.
好的   对不起
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
不用担心   我现在就去
- Don't worry about it.
- Just-just leave me.
爆炸...是遥控触发的吗？
The explosion--
was it triggered remotely?
它完好无损
It's intact.
里面的人都有钥匙的副本
Whoever's inside
had a copy of the key.
我们会将居民留在大本营
We're holding
the residents in base camp.
至少我们可以保留的
At least the ones
we managed to hold on to.
我的急救人员把其他人录了下来
My first responders
got the others on tape.
好想法  搜索公寓怎么样？
Good thinking. What about
searching the condos?
我可以获得联邦搜查令
I could bring federal warrants.
我听说
I heard.
17次飞行却没有防毒面具？
17 flights and no gas mask?
你在这里浪费宝贵的医疗时间 法尔科
You're wasting precious
medical time here, Falco.
在全市范围内的医疗紧急情况中
In the middle of
a citywide medical emergency.
不会再发生了 先生
It won't happen again, sir.
忘记命令 吧  我们只会请求许可
Forget about the warrants.
We'll just ask permission.
如果有人感到紧张 那就是我们要找的人
Anyone gets antsy,
they're the ones we want.
好吧 先生们听好了
All right, people, listen up.
特别探员朗马克加入我们的行列
We're being joined
by Special Agent Lammark
来自该局的区域外地办事处
from the Bureau's
regional field office.
FBI 会协助我们
The FBI is gonna be
assisting us
进行调查
with this investigation.
谢谢
Thank you.
好的 在接下来的几个小时内
Okay, within
the next few hours,
你的办公桌会被数据淹没
your desks are gonna be
flooded with data,
其中大部分不可避免地是错误的
much of it inevitably false.
你也会听到很多意见
You're also gonna hear
a lot of opinions.
但意见从来没有抓住任何人
But opinions
never caught anyone,
所以记住某些偏见很重要......
so it's important to keep
certain preconceptions in mind
在对证据进行分类时
while classifying evidence.
“杀人犯想被抓 ”
"Mass murderers
want to get caught."
好吧 不是这个
Well, this one doesn't.
29名受害者
29 victims.
每一枪都找到了目标
Every shot found its mark.
没有外壳 没有黄铜
No casings, no brass.
没有一根散乱的头发或指纹
Not a single stray hair
or fingerprint.
这人做事细心
This guy is thorough.
他不是来这里死的
He didn't come here to die,
他不想被发现
and he does not want
to be found.
我们会让他失望的
We're gonna disappoint him.
你会听到这个人被称为恐怖分子
You will hear this man
called a terrorist.
但任何恐怖组织
But any terrorist organization
那可以把它拉下来......
that could've
pulled that off...
……他们会争先恐后地为自己争光
...they would rush
to claim credit for it.
到目前为止 还没有
So far, none have.
你会听到这个人被称为疯子
You will hear this man
called a maniac.
妈的 我同意
Shit, I agree.
除了人格障碍的范围
Except the range
of personality disorders
范围如此之广 包括我们这里的所有人
is so extensive that
it includes all of us here.
抑郁 焦虑
Depression, anxiety,
呃 精神分裂症
uh, schizophrenia.
但...
- But...
偏执型人格障碍、自恋型人格障碍
PPD, NPD,
创伤后应激障碍
PTSD.
如果我们把街上所有的“疯子”都赶走..
We took every crazy
off the street,
没有人留下来监视他们
there would be no one left
to police them.
所以...
- So...
要想成功 我们必须保持开放的心态
to succeed, we're gonna
have to keep our minds open.
不要开始
Don't start out
想象一个种族主义者或纳粹分子
picturing a racist or a Nazi.
他不是一个类型
He's not a type.
他是一个人
He's a person.
有人喜欢它
Somebody loved him.
有人训练过他
Somebody trained him.
有人把那把枪卖给他
Somebody sold him that gun.
我们找到他们...
We find them...
我们找到了我们的人
we find our guy.
四...
Four...
市长正在为你
The governor's given you
他能给你的所有资源
all the resources
he can give you.
我无能为力了
There's nothing more I can do.
我是一名联邦特工
I'm a federal agent.
高速公路不是联邦的  抱歉   啊
Highways are not
federal. I'm sorry.
- Ah.
关闭它们只会引起大规模恐慌
Shutting them down
would only cause mass panic.
不 射手引起了大规模恐慌
No, the shooter
causes mass panic.
关闭高速公路会让人头疼
Shutting down a highway
causes headaches.
我的市长现在不需要头痛
Headaches my governor
doesn't need right now.
市长震惊地呼吁大家保持冷静
REPORTER [over TV]: In shock,
the mayor has called for calm.
如果你看到任何可疑的人...
If you see anyone suspicious...
“这不是一种类型 这是一个人 ”
"It's not a type.
It's a person."
真是个江湖骗子
What a hack.
他被赶出华盛顿特区我并不感到惊讶
No wonder
they kicked him out of D.C.
这些人 他们天生就是邪恶的
These people,
they're just born plain evil.
邪恶正在切断一只鸟的翅膀 只是为了看看会发生什么
Evil is cutting off a bird's
wing just to see what happens.
这家伙在拍蚊子
This guy is
swatting mosquitoes.
所有  我们应该抓住他的蛋蛋
Whatever. We should
string him up by his balls
把他吊在桅杆​​顶上
from the top of a flagpole.
这将阻止那里的所有其他疯子
That'll deter all the other
nutsos out there.
警官
Officer.
你为什么不把判决留给法官呢？
Why don't you leave
the sentencing to the judge.
我们现在的任务是抓住他
Our job right now
is to catch him.
对不起 先生   哦 没关系
- Sorry, sir.
- Oh, it's okay.
很高兴知道我将如何被记住
Nice to know
how I'll be remembered.
有机会喝点新鲜咖啡吗？
Any chance of
some fresh coffee?
这尝起来像刹车油
This tastes like
transmission fluid.
马上
Right away.
嗯 我会的
Mm, I'll do it.
没关系
It's okay.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你为什么这么说蚊子？
Why'd you say that thing
about mosquitoes?
哦 这只是一种感觉   基于什么？
- Oh, it was just a feeling.
- Based on what?
我不认为这家伙是在寻找破坏
I don't think this guy
is looking for destruction.
我认为他是在寻求解脱
I think
he's looking for relief.
你有预感他会再做一次吗？
And do you have a feeling
that he's gonna do it again?
是的
Yes.
为什么？
Why?
因为他喜欢
Because he liked it.
你怎么知道？
How do you know?
他杀了29人
He killed 29 people.
否则 两点后就会停下来
Otherwise, he would've
stopped at two.
好吧 他为什么完全停止射击？
Well, why did he stop
shooting at all?
我的意思是 为什么不杀五十或六十？
I mean, why not kill 50? 60?
是不是因为烟花停了
Was it because
the fireworks stopped
所以没有更多的枪声掩护？
and so there was no more cover
for the gunshots?
是的 也许吧   废话
- Yeah, maybe.
- Bullshit.
不要光顾我  告诉我你的想法
Don't patronize me.
Tell me what you think.
我认为他得到了他的满足
I think he got his fill.
不管饭菜有多好吃
No matter how good
the food tastes,
吃饱了就停止进食
you stop eating
when you've had enough.
直到你又饿了
Till you get hungry again.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
埃莉诺·法尔科 长官
Eleanor Falco, sir.
拉马克
Lammark.
这个国家死于枪支的人数......
WOMAN [on TV]: The number of
deaths by firearms in this...
也许是因为我们用谎言将伊拉克夷为平地？
MAN [on TV]: Maybe because
we leveled Iraq on a lie?
中国没有第二修正案
There's no
Second Amendment in China.
现在你在为大屠杀辩护？
Now you're
justifying mass murder?
不 我正在努力理解它
No, I'm trying
to understand it.
这在道德上没有歧义
There's no
moral ambiguity about it.
自杀或自残的死亡率...
The rate of death
by either suicide or homi...
...构建详尽的叙述
...construct
elaborate narratives
他们成为英雄
in which they get
to be the hero.
嘿
Hey.
伪突击队是恐怖分子
WOMAN [on TV]:
Pseudocommandos are terrorists
来历不明
without a known cause.
他们沉迷于武器和王权
They become obsessed
with weapons and regalia
来弥补自己的无能感和失败感
to make up for their own sense
of impotence and failure.
他们经常是侵略的受害者
MAN [on TV]: They're often
victims of aggression
在童年和成长过程中
during childhood
and development,
特别是来自人民
especially from the people
谁应该爱他们并保护他们
who are supposed to love
and protect them.
先生？
Sir?
朗马克有什么麻烦吗 法尔科？
Any trouble
with Lammark, Falco?
麻烦？
Trouble?
六点钟在林登布拉特与他会合
Meet him at Lindenblatt's
at 6:00.
他想见你  没说为什么
He wants to see you.
Didn't say why.
他妈的
Fuck.
我们让更多的人面临更大的风险
We are exposing
more people to more risk.
这是不可能的
It's out of the question.
你可以忘记它
You can forget about it.
杰西 你没看过《大白鲨》吗？
Jesse, haven't you seen "Jaws"?
现在 你就是混蛋
Right now, you're the asshole
那是在努力保持海滩开放
that's trying to keep
the beach open.
29具尸体
29 bodies.
好吧 他们在维加斯有 58 个
Well, they had 58 in Vegas.
第二天 席琳·迪翁出现了……
Next day, you had Celine Dion--
她在 凯撒宫舞台上
she's onstage, Caesars Palace.
演出必须继续进行   你在做什么？
- The show's got to go on.
- Hello.
那个人已经死了
That guy was dead.
我们有一名奥林匹克级狙击手在逃
We have an Olympic-class
marksman running wild.
市长不会关闭医院
The governor
is not closing hospitals,
不会关闭学校  好的  当然
- is not closing down schools.
Fine. Of course.
我们可以解决这个问题 但游乐园
Those we can deal with,
but theme parks,
商场、体育馆？
malls, stadiums?
是的 好吧 我们不会实施宵禁
Yeah, well, we're not gonna
impose a curfew
在没有任何线索的情况下
without a single clue.
策略是什么？
What's the strategy?
“直到拉马克找到他”？
"Until Lammark finds him"?
到现在为止 这家伙可能在明尼苏达州
By now, the guy could be
in Minnesota.
他们不会关闭明尼苏达州   哦
- They're not closing Minnesota.
- Oh.
9/11 纽约市...他们没有关闭它
9/11, New York City--
they didn't shut it down.
-听着 如果你不能兑现你的承诺
-Look, if you can't
deliver what you promised
没有关闭整个该死的城市
without shutting down
the whole damn city,
忘掉它   杰西
- forget about it.
- Jesse.
冷静下来
Calm down.
我能找到他
I can find him.
我需要知道的是你是否站在我这边
What I need to know
is that you're onside.
我要走了
I got to go.
市长在续集中仍然是市长
Mayor was still mayor
in the sequel.
这就是《大白鲨》的教训
That's the lesson from "Jaws."
让我们今天晚些时候恢复
- Let's revert later today.
我什至不知道那是什么意思
I don't even know
what that means.
天哪 他妈的
Jesus fuck.
先生
Sir.
嗯...
Um...
这是个好时机吗？
is this a good time?
不谢谢  请继续
No, please. Please, go ahead.
这些该死的人
These fucking people.
就好像他们设计了一个系统
It's almost as though
they designed a system
专门用来耗尽我的能量
specifically to drain
my energy away.
我不明白这一点  他们不想让你抓住他吗？
I don't get it. Don't they
want you to catch him?
当然 就在昨天
Oh, yeah. By yesterday.
问题是他们认为他们知道怎么做
The problem is that
they think they know how.
最后 说说你吧
Anyway, let's talk about you.
咖啡？
Coffee?
当然
Sure.
我可以想到两个原因
I can think of two reasons
为什么你可能会很好地了解这个人
why you might be getting
a good read on this guy.
你有潜力成为一名优秀的侦探
You're potentially
a good detective.
你和他一样脑子进水了
You're as fucked-up
in the head as he is.
不管怎样 我都是在帮大家一个忙
Either way,
I'm doing everyone a favor
让你远离街头
by keeping you off the streets.
哦
Oh.
嘿   你好
- Hey.
- Hi.
看着你 伙计  是什么让你这么苗条？
Look at you, buddy.
What's got you so slim?
放弃麸质  这是魔法
Cut out gluten.
It's a magic bullet.
面筋 是吧？  是的
- That gluten, huh?
- Yeah.
牛排和鸡蛋含有麸质？  不
- Steak and eggs got gluten?
- No.
我相信你见过杰克·麦肯齐？
I believe you've met
Jack McKenzie?
作为一名调查员 坦率地说
- As an investigator, frankly,
他充其量是平庸的
he's average at best.
但是当我们接近那个杀手时
But when we get close
to that killer,
相信我 我们都想要麦克
trust me,
we all want Mac around.
受宠若惊
- Flattered.
她留下来？
She staying?
我不得不要求你转账
I'd have to ask
for your transfer.
你会为联邦调查局工作吗？
I'd be working for the Bureau?
不 你基本上是我和巴尔的摩警方之间的联络人
No, you'd be a liaison
between BPD and me, basically,
确保我得到我需要的信息
making sure that I get
the information I need
当我需要的时候
when I need it.
我被豺狼和小丑包围着
I'm surrounded
by jackals and clowns.
克虏伯和马昆德有能力
Krupp and Marquand are capable,
但他们会向华盛顿特区报告一切
but they're gonna feed
everything back to D.C.
我只需要身边的人
I just need people around me
聪明且值得信赖的人
that are smart
and that I can trust.
现在 信不信由你 那就是你们两个
Right now, believe it or not,
that's you two.
所以不要搞砸了
So don't fuck it up.
做一个艺术家 而不是一个警察
Be an artist, not a cop.
运用你的直觉
Use your intuition.
这家伙正处在毁灭的漩涡中
This guy's on
a spiral of destruction.
我希望你能全身心投入
I expect you
to slide down after him.
我是来抓你的  你懂的
I'm here to catch you.
You know that.
你离这个女孩远点
You stay away from this girl.
谢谢你 先生 但我可以保护自己
Thank you, sir,
but I can protect myself.
哦 我很担心他
Oh, I'm worried about him.
好的 先生们
Okay, people.
我们去抓他吧
Let's go catch him.
这个街区有 12 个安全摄像头
The block has
12 security cameras,
但是磁盘每 72 小时就会被覆盖一次
but the drive overwrites
every 72 hours.
如果我们的人先进来 我们就失去了他
Our guy got in before that,
we missed him.
也有明显的盲区
There are also
significant blind spots,
包括服务区
including the service bay
还有二楼走廊的窗户
and the second-floor
hallway window.
现在 萨曼莎正在整理事件的所有图像
Now, Samantha's collating
all the incident AV:
手机、无人机、监控摄像头
cell phones,
drone surveillance.
这是大约300小时的视频
It's about 300 hours
of footage.
我们应该把它清理干净
We should have it cleaned up
并在下午 1点之前按顺序清理和编辑它们
and cut down in sequence
by 1:00 p.m.
我可以在 11点看到粗剪吗？
Can I see a rough cut at 11:00?
没问题  房地产经纪人正在检查
Absolutely.
The Realtor's checking through
过去六个月的所有演练
all of the walk-throughs
over the last six months.
他和他的团队将接受讯问
He and his team will be
available for questioning
明天早上第一时间
first thing tomorrow morning.
好的 油漆工 锁匠 电话公司
Okay, painters, locksmith,
phone company.
快点   没有固定电话 没有电缆 没有 Wi-Fi
- Come on.
- No landline,
no cable, no Wi-Fi.
没有人住在那里
No one lived there.
业主在大流行之前就已经粉刷过这个地方
The owner had the place painted
before the pandemic.
我们找到了公司  我们正在追踪这些人
We found the company.
We're tracing the men.
嗯 埃莉诺？
Um, Eleanor?
呃 你-您将收到所有这些报告的副本 是吗？
Uh, you-you're gonna get copies
of all these reports, okay?
是的 好吧
Yeah, all right.
嗯...拜托
Um... please.
奥尔特加先生 曾经是一名看门人
Señor Ortega has been a janitor
自开业以来就在这座大楼里
at this building
since it opened.
他今年 54 岁 古巴人 火药痕迹阴性
He's 54, Cuban, GPR negative.
没有枪 没有犯罪记录
There's no guns, no record.
声称他从来没有钥匙的副本
He claims he's never had a copy
是的
- of the keys.
Right.
还有一个看门人
There's another janitor
名叫巴拉萨上夜班
named Barraza,
works the night shift.
他放假了 所以联系不上
He was off on holiday,
so he's unreachable.
巴拉扎在哪里？
Where is Barraza?
他不在该地区
He's not in the area.
我没有问他不在哪儿  我问他在哪里
I didn't ask where he isn't.
I asked where he is.
不符合我们的形象
Doesn't fit our profile.
他很友善 很有趣
He's friendly, funny.
一半的居民指责他
Half of the residents
accused him
在走廊里抽大麻
of smoking weed in the hallway.
另一半呢？  他们是从他那里买的
- What about the other half?
- They're buying it from him.
很多笑声  克虏伯？
- Lot of laughter. Krupp?
我们已经对大楼的居民进行了身份验证
We've I.D.'d
the building's residents
并发起背景调查   嗯嗯
- and instigated
background checks.
- Mm-hmm.
反恐部门正在处理资料
Counterterrorism are processing
the profiles right now.
反恐？
Counterterrorism?
弗兰克格雷伯要求他们
Frank Graber requested them.
我负责处理
I run the operation.
不是弗兰克·格雷伯
Not Frank Graber.
不是华盛顿特区 当然不是你
Not D.C. Certainly not you.
他们的资源是我们的两倍
They have twice our resources.
我想你会同意的
I thought you'd be on board.
我只是想加快速度
I'm just trying
to speed things along.
我会加速你的屁股出门
I'll speed your ass
out the door.
如果弗兰克·格雷伯请求复苏
If Frank Graber
requests resuscitation,
你首先需要我的批准
you need my approval first.
好吗？
Okay?
这对每个人都适用
- That goes for everyone.
现在是什么情况？
What is it now?
确认你不是
Confirmation that you are not
要求宵禁
requesting a curfew.
杰西·卡普尔顿要你签名
Jesse Capleton
asked you to sign.
为什么我要签署
Why would I sign something
这与我要求的完全相反？
that's the exact opposite
of what I asked for?
他说你在会议上同意了
He said you agreed to
in the meeting,
现在他需要你以书面形式
- and now he needs you
on the record.
他妈的混蛋
Fucking asshole.
好的  马昆德？
Okay. Marquand?
是的先生  跟我直说
Yes, sir.
Be straight with me.
你一直在谈论反恐吗？
Have you been talking
to counterterrorism?
没有 先生
No, sir.
你打算继续这样吗？
Is it gonna stay that way?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
那你得到了什么？
Then what you got?
好吧 冲击波分析证实了
Well, the shockwave analysis confirmed
使用手榴弹
the use of a hand grenade.
这是一把M14
It's an M14.
他打开煤气 拉动别针
He turned on the gas,
pulled the pin,
走出去 他关上身后的门   嗯嗯
- walked out, and he closed
the door behind him.
- Mm-hmm.
锁下面也有很多划痕
There's also a lot of scratches
under the lock.
就像他有一大串钥匙
Like he had
a big bunch of keys.
现在 弹道学已将资金投入到 XM21 狙击系统上
Now, ballistics has their money
set on an XM21 sniper system.
从越南使用到波斯湾战争
Used in Vietnam,
right up to Desert Storm.
他们在 1975 年更新了瞄准具
They updated the scope in '75,
但我们认为它是原件之一
but we think
it's one of the originals.
如果是这样的话 我们 呃……我们有麻烦了
If that's the case, we, uh...
we got a problem.
那是什么？
What's that?
这把枪比数据库还旧
The gun is older
than the database.
这意味着我们将不得不用老式的方式来做
That means we're gonna
have to go old-school,
手动匹配每个证据
match each piece of evidence manually
有各州的军事档案
with military archives
state by state.
这是飓风中的屁  ...很有诗意
- It's a fart in a hurricane.
- That's very poetic.
这是我妻子说的
That's what my wife says.
军队如何处理
What does the Army do
with weapons
不再使用的武器？
that are no longer in use?
如果他们身体状况良好
If they're in decent condition,
他们将被移交给当地警方
they get kicked down
to local law enforcement.
有些被拆除 有些被重新分配
Some get dismantled,
others get redistributed
到世界各地的武装盟军
to armed allied forces
around the world.
谁拆除它们？
Who dismantles them?
呃 军火库管理员  每个基地单位都有一个
Uh, the arsenal keepers.
Every base unit has one.
但是谁能证明它们确实被摧毁了呢？
But who actually verifies
that they're destroyed?
你知道吗？ 从保管人处获取文件
You know what?
Get the keeper records.
现役、起诉、遗失武器、
Active duty, prosecutions,
missing weapons,
心理创伤 创伤后应激障碍  我们正在努力
- psych trauma, PTSD.
We're on it.
我们都需要更多的帮助 内森
We can all use more help, Nathan,
但我需要合作 而不是竞争
but I need collaboration,
not competition.
必须有明确的指挥链
There has to be
a clear chain of command.
个人问题？
Personal question?
你不觉得朗马克有点偏执吗
Don't you think
Lammark's a bit paranoid
关于其他团队的参与？
about other teams
being involved?
并不确切  每个人都在寻找信用
Not really.
Everyone's looking for credit.
我见过太多因误伤而出轨的案例
I've seen way too many cases
derail from friendly fire.
我的天哪
My God.
告诉我你在这里有东西
Tell me you got something here.
身高体重什么的
Height, weight, anything.
那个距离...我什至无法开始推测
That distance-- I can't even
start to speculate.
小入口 大出口
Small entrance,
large exit on all.
每个受害者一枪
One shot per victim.
头、胸、脖子...枪
Head, chest, neck-- gone.
都是你的 朋友   是的
- All yours, my friend.
- Yeah.
你见过这样的东西吗 麦克？
You ever seen anything
like this, Mac?
从来没有离开过军队
Not outside the Army.
里面很少见
Very few inside.
我的意思是 你有风 烟花让你分心
I mean, you got wind,
fireworks distracting you.
这十分完美
It's flawless.
有人知道这家伙有多好
Someone knows
how good this guy is.
高水平的军事或运动训练
Military-trained
or high-level sports.
无论哪种方式
Either way,
这是赢得奖牌
this is winning medals.
枪手是男的？
Is the shooter a man?
是的
Yes.
为什么？
Why?
在这个规模？
At this scale?
没有先例
Unprecedented.
有计划的还是自发的？
Planned or spontaneous?
计划中   自发的
Planned.
Spontaneous.
那他为什么会有武器？
Then why did he have a weapon?
他擅自闯入
He was trespassing.
也许他在等警察
Maybe he was expecting
the police.
用一把40年的狙击步枪？
With a 40-year-old
sniper rifle?
不同性别 不同种族
Different genders,
different races.
有些老了 有些还很年轻
Some old, some quite young.
没有模式
There's no pattern.
为什么？
Why?
好吧 我们可以推测
Well, we can speculate
因为你不责怪自然
that nature's not to blame.
责怪文化
Culture is.
我们都是不同的
We're all different.
我们的行为是一样的
We still act the same.
高峰时间 午餐时间
Rush hour, lunch hour,
黑色星期五 新年前夜
Black Friday, New Year's Eve.
我们只是盲目地遵循相同的模式
We just blindly follow
the same patterns.
他不是在惩罚人
He's not punishing people.
他正在破坏行为
He's disrupting behavior.
没有折磨 没有陶醉在痛苦中
There's no torture,
no reveling in the suffering.
只是一张去纳尼亚的快速单程票
Just a-- poof--
quick one-way ticket to Narnia.
先生
Sir.
他们有他
They have him.
你是什​​么意思 “他们有他”？ 谁有他？
What do you mean,
"They have him"? Who has him?
老实说
Frank?
在内森另有说明之前 我将负责此事
I'm heading this up
till Nathan says otherwise.
嘿 不要心脏病发作
Hey, don't have a heart attack.
我不是来除掉你的
I'm not here to undermine you.
我们只需要快速行动
- We just have to move fast.
我们正在检查居民
We're checking up
the residents,
这个人正在敲响所有警钟
and this kid rings alarm bells
all over the place.
我们试图审问他 他把自己锁在房间里
We try to question him,
he locks himself in his room
并威胁要杀死所有人 这绝不是一个好兆头
and threatens to kill everyone,
which is never a good sign.
阿尔法小队 就位
OFFICER [over radio]:
Alpha Team, into position.
贝塔 团队 清理地板
Beta Team, clear the floor.
我们看到武器了吗？
OFFICER 2 [over radio]:
Do we have eyes on the weapon?
重复 武器确认了吗？
Repeat,
is the weapon confirmed?
很高兴你在打电话给我之前邀请了所有人！
It was nice of you to invite
everyone before calling me!
他勾选了每个方框：多动症
He ticks every box: ADHD,
因为被欺负而逃学
skips school
because he gets bullied,
整晚都在看 ISIS 的视频
spends all night
watching ISIS clips
并在电子游戏上大发雷霆
and blowing out brains
on video games.
去年夏天 他的叔叔阿齐兹带他去了射击俱乐部
And his uncle Aziz took him
to the gun club last summer.
这是租客们的地方
This is where the tenants
红杉街12 号的居民 他们留在他们的税收
of 12 Redwood Street
are staying on your dime.
现在看来 凶手就在其中
Now it seems the killer
is among them.
他是怎么进入公寓的？
How'd he access the apartment?
拉赫马尼斯...他们住在它上面
The Rahmanis--
they live above it.
他本可以爬到窗台上  他熟悉这个地区
He could've climbed to
the ledge. He knows the area.
大概是策划好了这一切
Probably planned out
this whole thing.
准备出发  20 秒
SWAT COMMANDER [over radio]:
Ready to go. 20 seconds.
收到
Copy that.
阿尔法小队 我们进去了
Alpha Team, we're going in.
我们确定他有武器吗？
Do we know for certain
that he's armed?
他说他要杀了所有人！
He said he was gonna
kill everyone!
我问他有没有带枪 不是他说的！
I asked whether he was armed,
not what he said!
那个公寓里有一张床垫
There was a mattress
in that condo.
如果他住在楼上 为什么会有一个？
Why would there be one
if he lived upstairs?
她是谁？ 她怎么会在这里？
Who is this?
Why is she even here?
没关系 埃莉诺
It's okay, Eleanor.
三、二、一
SWAT COMMANDER [over radio]:
In three, two, one.
走！走！走！
Go, go, go!
你同意了吗？
Did you give the go-ahead?
退后 拉马克！
Back off, Lammark!
趴下！  趴下！
- Get down on the floor!
- Get down!
武器在哪里？
Where's the weapon?
他妈的呆在原地！
Stay the fuck
right where you are!
...我什么都没做！  你他妈的在做什么？
- I didn't do anything!
- What the fuck are you doing?
带上网
Get a life mat.
他要去窗户了！
He's going for the window!
他要去他妈的窗户！
He's going for
the fucking window!
撒网！
- Get a life mat!
你的税金正在支付他们的客房服务
Your tax dollars are
paying for their room service.
现在看来 凶手一直就在他们中间
Now it seems the killer
has been among them all along.
武器在哪里 弗兰克？
Where's the weapon, Frank?
到目前为止 你还没有找到弹射器
So far, you haven't found
a catapult.
他可以把它藏在任何地方
He could've stashed it anywhere.
你没有枪支
You don't have a firearm.
你离建立任何联系都很遥远
You're oceans away from
establishing any connection
特别是对旧的 XM21 步枪
to an old XM21 rifle
in particular.
你不会成为一流的狙击手
You don't get to become
a first-class marksman
通过玩电子游戏
playing video games.
所以 你要么在这里找到一些证据
So, you either find
some evidence here,
有点意思
make some sense of it,
还是你承认...
or admit that this has been
这是一个巨大的错误
a colossal fuckup!
来吧 拉马克
Come on, Lammark.
如果不是他 他为什么要跳楼？
If it wasn't him,
how come he jumped?
我不知道 也许是因为那该死的寄生虫
I don't know, maybe it's
'cause of that fucking parasite
吉米·基特里奇在电视直播中称他为恐怖分子
Jimmy Kittridge calling him
a terrorist on live TV.
一个阿拉伯孩子 在巴尔的摩的一所高中
Arab kid,
Baltimore high school.
你认为他画的是他自己吗
Do you think
he pictured himself
之后成为返校王？
becoming homecoming king
after that?
好吧 但现在 可能是他 对吧？
Okay, but for now,
it could've been him, right?
我的意思是 直到他被证明是无辜的？
I mean, until
he's proven innocent?
杰西 它应该是相反的
Jesse, it's supposed to be
the other way around.
不是当我们与其他六个州竞争时
Not when we're competing
with six other states
一个价值 90 亿美元的天然气厂
for a $9 billion gas plant.
我需要外面的人感到安全 朗马克
I need the people out there
to feel safe, Lammark.
这说明我们在行动  它为我们节省了更多时间
This shows them we're on it.
It buys us more time.
你要把那些该死的告诉拉赫曼尼人吗？
Are you gonna tell that shit
to the Rahmanis?
去告诉他们
Go ahead, tell 'em that,
因为我他妈的有工作要做
'cause I got
fucking work to do.
三位画家在公寓里工作
Three painters worked
the apartment.
我们有罗德尼·朗
We've got Rodney Lang,
亚伯拉罕·海恩斯和迪米特里·博夫罗夫
Abraham Haynes
and Dimitri Bovrov.
朗先生 这应该很快
Mr. Lang, this should be quick.
希望你不会介意  呃 我带来了增援
I hope you don't mind.
Uh, I brought backup.
我的妻子工作双班制 所以...
Wife's working a double, so...
猜猜谁在这里负责小德斯蒙德
guess who's in charge
of little Desmond here.
戴斯蒙德 是吗？
Desmond, huh?
有一个叔叔叫戴斯蒙德
Had an uncle called Desmond.
曾经写情色小说
Used to write erotic novels
under the, uh, name
笔名“旋律爆炸 ”
"Melody Bangs."
好的  -我想你记得昨晚你在哪里？
Okay. -I suppose you remember
where you were last night?
嗯 是的  其实我们...
Uh, yeah. Actually, we...
去港口看烟花
went down to the harbor
to watch the fireworks.
我们到过那里  可怕的 该死的
We were there. Scary shit.
你有……你有证据？
You got... you got proof?
证据？  嗯嗯
- Proof?
- Mm-hmm.
我们得到了证据 是的
We got proof, yeah.
就像一百万张自拍照
Like a million selfies.
在我婆婆家
ABRAHAM [voice-over]:
At my mother-in-law's.
我以为你抓住了那个人
I thought you caught the guy.
或许  没有照片？
Maybe. No pictures?
嗯...
Mm...
我婆婆家
ABRAHAM [voice-over]:
Of my mother-in-law?
很多照片
Lots of pictures.
这是一个盛大的聚会  堂兄弟 侄子
Big party. Cousins, nephews.
我在这是要干嘛？ 我是嫌疑人吗？
What am I doing here?
Am I a suspect?
我只是把这该死的地方拆开了
I just stripped
the fucking place.
两年前
Two years ago.
嘿嘿嘿  冷静下来
Hey, hey, hey. calm down.
一切都很好
It's all good.
他只会问你问题
Just asking you questions.
我一个人在我的公寓里
I was at my apartment alone.
放轻松 迪米特里
Relax, Dimitri.
在这个国家独自过夜仍然是合法的
It's still legal to spend
a night alone in this country.
你能证明这个吗？
- Can you prove it?
我的 呃 邻居 也许他看到我进来了？
My, uh, neighbor,
maybe he see me come in?
而且 呃 我打电话给我在俄罗斯的父亲
And, uh,
I call my father in Russia.
也许你可以向电话公司核实一下？
Perhaps you can verify
with phone company?
但你确实得到了一些...
But you did get some...
你在俄罗斯进行一些军事训练 对吧？
some military training
in Russia, right?
你做了一些目标练习吗？
Did you get
any shooting practice?
先生 我没有杀那些人
Sir, I did not kill
those people.
我觉得我需要向你解释这件事是可耻的
I find it shameful that I need
to explain this to you.
我是一个诚实的人
I'm an honest man,
我为我所拥有的而努力工作
and I work hard
for what I have.
是的 我进行了射击练习...两周
Yes, I did shooting practice--
two weeks.
然后我断了我的胳膊 所以不适合射击
Then I break my arm,
so no good for shooting.
他们叫我去打扫营房 所以我打扫
They tell me to go
clean barracks, so I sweep,
我擦窗户 这就是我为国家服务的方式
I wash windows, and that is
how I serve my country.
海恩斯先生 你为什么停止工作
Mr. Haynes,
why did you stop working
在豪华喷漆和修复？
at DeLuxe Painting and Repairs?
也许我不够快
Maybe I wasn't fast enough.
你得问问他们
You'd have to ask them.
所以 你……所以你把这个地方拿下来了
So, you...
you stripped the place.
一个人   是的
- Alone.
- Yes.
你还记得什么？
What else do you remember?
那光
That light.
风景
The view.
我们一起在休息室工作
We worked the lounge together.
然后迪米特里为卧室留了额外的钱
Then Dimitri stayed extra
for the bedrooms.
我认为
I think.
不 我我粉刷了卧室
No, I did the bedrooms.
我敢肯定
- I'm sure.
埃莉诺 你会认为这是我的性别歧视吗
Eleanor, would you
consider it sexist of me
如果我让你带小德斯蒙德来这里
if I asked you
to take little Desmond here
让他睡觉？
and put him to sleep?
哦  谢谢亲爱的
Oh. Thanks, sweetie.
朗先生 您的能力相当 呃...
Mr. Lang, you've got
quite the, uh...
你画墙的功夫不错吧？
the gig
in wall painting, right?
你经常为豪华房工作
You're a regular at DeLuxe.
你也经常为紫外工作吗？
A string of work
for Ultraviolet as well?
好吧 呃 孩子们并不便宜
Well, uh,
kids don't come cheap.
你好  打扰一下
Hi. Excuse me.
初步实验室报告
Preliminary lab report.
哦   介意帮我签个名吗？
- Oh.
- Mind signing it for me?
好的  当然   谢谢
- Okay. Sure.
- Thanks.
惊人的  谢谢
Awesome. Thank you.
不 伙计们 请  伙计们！
No, guys, please. Guys!
你要调查吗
Do you want an investigation,
或者你想要一个娱乐活动？
or do you want
an entertainment event?
嘿 埃莉诺
Hey, Eleanor.
你收到实验室寄来的包裹了吗？
Did you receive
a package from the lab?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
我已将其包含在我的报告中
I've included it in my report.
尿液和粪便样本稀少
The urine and fecal samples
were scarce,
但仍然足以检测缺铁
but there was still enough
to detect an iron deficiency.
我查了一下
I looked it up, and it's common
在不吃肉的人中间很常见
amongst people
who don't eat meat.
几点到的？
What time did it arrive?
我不知道 20 分钟还是 45分钟前？
- I don't know, 20 minutes ago?
- 45.
我不知道 所以 呃 我给实验室打了电话
I didn't have it,
so, uh, I rang the lab.
与快递员确认   对不起 先生
- Checked with the courier.
- I'm sorry, sir.
我只是想帮忙  你在打电话 然后...
I was just trying to help.
You were on the phone, and...
这是专门的 紧急的
This is specialized, urgent,
机密信息
classified intel.
你是巴尔的摩警方的联络人 一个巡逻警察
You are the BPD liaison,
a beat cop,
没有大学学位 但你决定
no college degree,
but you decide
我应该等等你的判决
that I should wait
for your verdict.
埃莉诺 对不起 我太激动了
Eleanor, I'm sorry I snapped.
我的电话交谈压力大得离谱
I had a ridiculously stressful
phone conversation.
我拿你出气了   不用担心
- I took it out on you.
- No worries.
嘿 我知道已经晚了
Hey, I know it's late,
但我有 呃 一些新东西要讲
but I have, uh,
some new stuff to go over,
我可以利用你的智慧
and I could use
some of your brain.
想过来吃晚饭
Want to come have some dinner,
并喝一杯好酒 谈一谈？
talk it through
with a good glass of wine?
先生 如果你雇我是为了操我
Sir, if you hired me
so you could fuck me,
你可以接受这份工作 你可以把它推到你的屁股上
you can take this job and
you can shove it up your ass.
埃莉诺 我结婚了
Eleanor, I'm married.
来和我们一起吃晚饭吧
Come and have dinner with us.
你看起来需要一顿美餐
You look like you could use
a good meal.
你也认为它会再次发生
You also think
it's gonna happen again.
你为什么要签署这份备忘录？
Why did you sign that memo?
你不可能打每一场仗
You can't fight every battle.
必须选择你能赢的那些
Have to choose
the ones you can win.
是的 但当你签约时 你就是游戏的一部分
Yeah, but when you sign,
you're a part of the game.
当你不这样做时 他们就会取代你
And when you don't,
they replace you.
你做的唯一决定
The only decision you're making
是埋葬还是火葬
is whether
to be buried or burned.
杰西卡普尔顿不能解雇你
Jesse Capleton can't fire you.
他不是你的老板
He's not your boss.
杰西卡普尔顿操纵着我的老板
Jesse Capleton
operates my boss,
谁经营他作为回报
who operates him in return.
像他们这样的人 他们总是意见一致
Guys like that,
it's a circle jerk.
只需要一个电话就够了
All it takes is one call.
“你不觉得朗马克 有点不对劲吗？”
"Don't you think Lammark's
a little off his game?"
“好吧 没有比我更大的粉丝了
"Well, there is
no bigger fan than me,
但我们确实必须考虑他的心 ”
but we do have to think
of his heart."
他们每个人都说对方想听的话
They each say what
the other one wants to hear.
在你知道之前
Before you know it,
你正在把你的办公桌装进一个盒子里
you're packing your desk
into a box.
我的拙见？  嗯嗯？
- Humble opinion?
- Mm-hmm?
这不是因为他们害怕你不会抓住他
It's not 'cause they're scared
you won't catch him.
这是因为他们害怕你会这样做
It's 'cause
they're scared you will.
如果你解决了它 你就会成为众人瞩目的焦点
You crack this,
you get the spotlight.
有些人就是受不了阴影
Some people just can't stand
the shadows.
郎朗有些古怪
There's something odd
about Lang.
手表 鞋子
The watch, the shoes,
带宝宝进来
bringing the baby in.
不是朗  他的不在场证明是可靠的
It's not Lang.
His alibi's solid.
但我早上会打电话给特蕾西
But I'll call Tracey
in the morning
如果你想监控他的通讯
if you want to monitor
his comm.
你结婚多久了？
How long have you been married?
自从我们被允许
Ever since we were allowed.
这是个大问题
That's the big question:
人们如何塑造系统 系统如何塑造我们
how people shape systems,
how systems shape us.
我可以给你一点吗...
Can I get you a little...
哦 只是水 谢谢
- Oh, just water, thank you.
今天 一切都与地位有关
Today, it's all about status.
拥有它的人会为了保护它而杀戮
The people that have it
would kill to protect it,
想要它的人会为了实现它而杀戮
the people that want it
would kill to achieve it,
其他人都在中间被压垮了
and everybody else
gets crushed in between.
政府、企业和学校
Governments, corporations
and high schools.
模式似乎是一样的
Pattern seems to be the same.
我们如何改变它？
How do we change that?
你的意思是同理心 联系？
You mean empathy, connection?
如果我们真的在别人身上看到自己
If we truly see ourselves
in others,
我们要提升他们 而不是让他们失望
we want to raise them up,
not bring them down.
如果我们没钱了
If we ever run out of money,
你要写冰箱贴
you are gonna write
fridge magnets.
我是认真的...你会很棒的
I'm serious--
you would be fantastic.
哦
Oh.
他们在说什么？
What are they saying?
你不想知道
You don't want to know.
加文 我确实想知道
Gavin, I do want to know.
这就是我问的原因
That's why I asked.
你知道该怎么做
You know the drill.
第一个 24 小时是：“这是谁干的？”
First 24 hours is:
"Who did this?"
在那之后 它是：
And then after that, it's:
“抓不到的白痴是谁？”
"Who's the idiot
that's not catching him?"
不 我的意思是理论
No, I meant the theory.
哦  是的   理论是什么？
- Oh. Right.
- What's the theory?
嗯嗯   恐怖分子的潜伏细胞
- Mm-hmm.
- Sleeper cells of terrorists
在每一个美国小镇
in every American town,
一项旨在废除公民自由法的内部工作
an inside job designed to scrap
civil liberties laws.
犹太人的阴谋？选择一个你想要的
Jewish plot? Take your pick.
你选择哪一个？
And what's yours?
这么好的问题
Such a good question.
让我看看   糟糕的电话
- Let me see.
- Bad call.
她问
She asked.
我想你的男人不是在这里出生的
I think your man
wasn't born here.
唔
Hmm.
我想他觉得他长大的地方
I think he feels
a place he grew up in
已经变成了一个非常糟糕的地方
has become
a pretty awful place,
以及世界上很大一部分... -嗯
along with a good portion
of the world... -Mm.
...我认为他相信这个国家有责任
...and I think he believes
this nation is responsible
至少占该灾难的 50%
for at least 50% of that mess.
该死的
Shit.
如果你不恐高
If you weren't afraid
of heights,
我会把你列为嫌疑人
I'd book you as a suspect.
让我害怕的是你的很大一部分
What scares me is that
a good portion of you
相信这个人是对的  嗯嗯
- thinks this man has a point.
Mm-hmm.
关于阻止纳粹的国家……
About the country
that stopped the Nazis...
嗯  是的  -...踏上月球
- Mm. Right.
- ...stepped on the moon,
绘制了整个人类基因组
mapped the entire human genome
并在火星上降落了一艘宇宙飞船
and landed a spacecraft on Mars
距您当前位置 2.25 亿公里
140 million miles
from your current position.
在登陆我们的品牌、我们的塑料、我们的变形的同时
While landing our brands,
our plastic, our distortion,
我们在其他地方的炒作！
our exaggeration
everywhere else.
我去波哥大讲课
I went to Bogotá to lecture.
地球上最好的该死的咖啡 对吧？
Best damn coffee
on Earth, right?
你知道他们把我带到哪里了吗？
You know where they took me?
星巴克
Starbucks.
我们把最好的地方
We take the best of everywhere,
为了利润 我们将其退回更糟
and we send it back worse
for profit.
这就是我们对朋友所做的
And that's what we do
to our friends.
利润纳税
Profits pay taxes,
支付研究和开发费用
which pays for
research and development.
埃莉诺...  加文 去睡觉
- Eleanor...
- Gavin, go to bed,
否则我会以骚扰两名公务员为由逮捕你
or I'll arrest you for
harassing two public servants.
我放弃  我放弃
- I give up. I give up.
那么 埃莉诺 你为什么要对我撒谎？
So, Eleanor,
why did you lie to me?
先生？
Sir?
你被联邦调查局拒绝了
You were rejected
by the Bureau.
你决定不告诉我？
You decided not to tell me?
那才是让我生气的 而不是实验室报告
That's what pissed me off,
not the lab report.
是的 那是八年前的事了
Yeah, it was eight years ago.
我认为这无关紧要
I didn't think it would matter.
我们在显微镜下
We're under the microscope.
一切都很重要
Everything matters.
我只是觉得我可以证明自己
I just thought
I could prove myself
在我被发现之前
before I got found out.
我应该告诉你的  对不起
I should have told you.
I'm sorry.
你擅长观察和知识
You aced observation
and knowledge.
是你的心理评估害了你
It was your psych eval
that did you in.
“好斗、上瘾、反社会 ”
"Aggressive, addictive,
antisocial."
这是我们逮捕的人的资料 而不是我们雇用的人的资料
This is the profile
of people we arrest, not hire.
你知道他们什么时候让你画一棵树吗？ -嗯嗯
You know when they ask you
to draw a tree? -Mm-hmm.
行李箱代表你到现在为止的生活
The trunk represents
your life up to the present.
是的   从这幅画来看
- Yeah.
- And from the picture,
卡茨博士推测是有什么东西把你搞砸了
Dr. Katz conjectured
that something fucked you up,
非常糟糕 大约 12 岁
and pretty badly,
around the age of 12.
没有土壤
There's no soil.
你的树没有根 也没有果子
Tree has no roots, no fruit.
当年是不是出什么事了？
Did something happen back then?
有这个必要吗？  这不是强制性的
- Is this necessary?
- It's not mandatory.
我只想知道我们是否应该解雇 卡茨博士
I just want to know
if we should fire Dr. Katz,
因为我认为你很有天赋
'cause I think you got talent.
“你有没有尝试过任何非法物质？”
"Have you ever tried
any illegal substances?"
“是的 ” “哪个？” “他们全部 ”
"Yes." "Which ones?"
"All of them."
那对你的申请也没有帮助
That didn't help
your application, either.
你在想什么？
What were you thinking?
在库尔特柯本 “我宁愿因为我是谁而被人讨厌
Kurt Cobain: "I'd rather
be hated for who I am
而不是因为我不是我而被爱 ”
than loved for who I'm not."
是的
Yeah.
根据联邦调查局的说法 他不完全是榜样
He's not exactly a role model,
according to the Bureau.
您曾在干洗店和呼叫中心工作
You worked at a dry cleaner's
and with a call center.
哎 怎么不找个更有前途的？
Hey, why didn't you look for
something with more prospects?
你很聪明 口齿伶俐
You're smart, articulate.
好吧 那并不重要
Well, that doesn't
count for much
当你没有上大学时
when you don't go to college.
那么 你为什么不呢？
So, why didn't you?
因为没有人为此买单
Because there was no one
to pay for it.
当你整天努力挣房租时
And when you work all day
trying to make rent,
你不想学习  你想睡觉
you don't feel like studying;
you feel like sleeping.
是什么促使你执法？
What led you
to law enforcement?
我在寻找保护
I was looking for protection.
从谁哪里？
From who?
从我自己
From myself.
对你来说够了吗？
That enough for you?
不
No.
埃莉诺...
Eleanor...
...对我来说唯一够了是稳固的领先优势
...the only thing enough for me
is a solid lead.
驱使我们射手的仇恨
The hatred
that drives our shooter
和你的没什么不同
isn't so different from yours.
与其出去消灭所有人 不如
Instead of going out there
and wiping everybody out,
你反对你自己
you turn it against yourself.
我需要你用它作为燃料给我带来新的东西
I need you to use it as fuel
to bring me something new.
现在
Now.
如果我们抓住这个家伙 其他一切都会消失
We get this guy,
this all goes away.
我们都可以完成我们本来要做的工作
And we can both do the job
we were meant to.
女士 你想美白牙齿吗？
Would you like your teeth
whitened, ma'am?
我们可以在现场进行
We can do it
right here on the spot.
今天不行   你会注意到不同之处
Not today.
- You'll notice the difference
只需五分钟   谢谢你亲爱的
- in just five minutes.
- Thank you, dear.
点亮你的小...
Brighten your sm...
女士们 如果你们渴望夏天
WOMAN [over P.A.]: Ladies,
if you're longing for summer,
是时候开始塑形了
it's time to start
getting in shape.
来二楼美容吧免费咨询
Come for a free consultation
in the second-floor beauty bar.
请不要离开
MAN [over P.A.]:
Please do not leave
任何无人看管的储物袋
any store bags unattended.
如果您发现任何可疑情况 请告诉我们的安全团队
If you see anything suspicious,
just tell our security team.
呃 抱歉
Uh, excuse me.
- Yes?
呃 我想你误拿了我的东西
Uh, I think you took my stuff
by mistake.
我自己的衣服
My own clothes.
你到底怎么了 兄弟？
What the hell is wrong
with you, bro?
呃 对不起
Uh, excuse me.
有个家伙
You got a guy giving himself
在后面的盆里洗个全身
a full body wash
in the basin back there.
嗯  -我的意思是 我猜他有问题
Uh-huh. -I mean,
I'm guessing he's got issues,
但说真的 不酷   是的 我明白了
- but seriously, not cool.
- Yeah, I got it.
有人能上第三层吗？
MAN [over radio]: Can we get
someone down to level three?
我-我这里有个人
I-I got a guy here.
呃 有人拿着他的衣服跑了
Uh, somebody ran off
with his clothes.
让我们打电话给总部  这里没有人
Let's call dispatch.
There's no one here.
我的天啊  他在做什么？
Oh, my God. What's he doing?
我厌倦了这些家伙   嘿
- I'm tired of these dudes.
- Hey.
你的自尊心在哪里？
Where's your sense
of self-respect?
你不是动物
You're not an animal.
忽略他  这是...  我...
- Ignore him. It's...
- I...
嘿！
Hey!
先生！
Sir!
先生 停在那里
Sir, stop right there.
拿住！
Hold it!
先生 我需要看看包里的东西
Gonna need to take a look
in the bag, sir.
不要让我们问两次
Don't make us ask twice.
打开包 先生
Just open the bag, sir.
我只是想回家   我知道你想回家
- I just want to go home.
- I know you want to go home.
我们只需要查看包中的内容即可
We just need to see
the contents of the bag.
拜托 你能为我们打开它吗？
Please, can you open
that up for us?
我只是想去   我们会让你走
- I just want to go.
- We'll let you go.
我们只需要你打开那个包
We just need you
to open that bag.
请立即打开包
Open the bag right now, please.
打开包   先生 不要让我再问了
Open the bag.
- Sir, don't make me ask again.
打开包  打开包！
- Open the bag.
Open the bag!
他妈的！
Fuck!
我已经很多年没见过 XM21 步枪了
I haven't seen
an XM21 in years,
但如果你知道去哪里找 它们就在附近
but they're around
if you know where to look.
我会在哪里看？
Where would I look?
国防部是唯一的政府部门
DoD's the only
government department
过去 25 年的每次审计都未通过
that's failed every audit
for the last 25 years.
他们丢失了价值 10 亿美元的武器
They lost track of a billion
dollars' worth of weapons
仅在伊拉克和科威特
in Iraq and Kuwait alone.
拉斯基先生 你为什么要买一把老式武器
Mr. Lassky, why would you buy
a vintage weapon
什么时候有更新的？
when there are
newer ones available?
嗯 很多时候 他们更好
Well, ofttimes, they're better.
易于装载 易于清洁 标准弹药
Easy load, easy clean,
standard ammo.
像 1853 年的恩菲尔德？
Like that 1853 Enfield?
是的
Yeah.
那是经典
That's a classic.
由同盟军使用
Used by the Confederate forces.
还有三K党
And the Ku Klux Klan.
听着 我在这里没有做任何违法的事情
Listen, I'm not doing
anything illegal here.
美国的历史...
The history of America...
牛奶或 BXP？ 在马里兰州？
Milkor BXP? In Maryland?
这是相当违法的
It's pretty illegal.
听着 拉斯基先生 我需要
Look, Mr. Lassky,
I'm gonna need
您所有客户的列表
a list of all of your clients.
如果这个人是他们中的一员
If this guy's one of them
而你隐瞒了这些信息...
and you withheld
that information...
这里有两支护理队
MAN [over radio]:
Got two paramedic teams here.
他们可以进去吗？ 收到
- Can they enter?
Copy that.
我们会派人护送  请问是哪个入口？
We'll send an escort.
Which entryway, please?
收到  好的 继续前进
Copy that. Okay, keep moving.
我们有一名 35 岁的黑人男性
OFFICER [over radio]:
We have a Black male, 35,
五点十 220磅...
- five-ten, 220 pounds...
他们听了吗？
Are they even listening?
盖伊身高超过六英尺 和我的屁股一样白
Guy's over six feet,
white as my ass.
是的  的 我会去清理它们
Yeah. I'll go set 'em straight.
我再说一遍
- OFFICER [over radio]:
- I repeat, ,
35岁 五点十 220磅……
35, five-ten, 220 pounds...
好的
Okay.
后备箱里有一把 357玛格南
...Magnum .357
in the back of his trunk.
这一定是我见过的最奇怪的事情了
That's got to be the weirdest
fucking thing I've ever seen.
与山姆交谈
Talk to Sam.
窗户中的倒影 商店中的相机
Reflections in windows,
cameras in stores.
我们应该能够得到这个人的 3D 打印输出
We should be able to get
a 3D printout of this guy.
抱歉 没有……里面没有摄像头
Sorry, there's no...
there's no cameras in there.
还没有
Not yet.
等等  退后
W-W-Wait. Rewind that.
那是他的衬衫
- That's his shirt.
带我去那个洗手间   好 当然
- Take me to that restroom.
- Yeah, sure.
他不是来这里杀人的
He didn't come here to kill.
他来这里吃饭
He came here to eat.
去买新衣服
To get new clothes.
清理
To clean up.
一只知道剩菜在哪里的狗
A dog who knows
where the leftovers are.
足够聪明 不会留下任何指纹
Smart enough
not to leave any fingerprints.
他只是在挑蔬菜吗？ -是的
Is he just picking out
the vegetables? -Yeah.
你缺铁
There's your iron deficiency.
我们的狗是食草动物
Our dog is a herbivore.
我的天啊！
Christ.
枪法
The marksmanship.
酷得像他妈的黄瓜
Cool as a fucking cucumber.
他不想参与
He doesn't want to engage.
这就像他妈的“吃豆人”
This is like fucking "Pac-Man."
谁训练了他？
Who trained him?
不是军队
Not the Army.
武器是他的延伸
Weapons are an extensionof hims.
他出生在他们之中
He was born among 'em.
这里有坏消息
McKENZIE [over radio]:
Bad news here.
它是什么？ 保洁员
What is it?
The cleaning crew
在拍摄开始之前通过
came through
before the shooting began.
卡车把他们俩都接走了   这不可能
The trucks pick up at 2:00.
我的天啊   他们去哪里？
Oh, my God.
- Where do they go?
啊
Ugh.
我不知道我会先发生什么...
I can't tell what's gonna
happen to me first--
我要心脏病发作了
I'm gonna have a heart attack,
否则我会被解雇  是的
- or I'm gonna get fired.
Yeah.
嗯 谢谢你的安慰
Well, thanks
for the reassurance.
你只是偏执狂
You're just being paranoid.
听着 如果我不是
Look, in case I'm not,
与 麦肯齐 并肩工作
work side by side
with McKenzie.
停下那辆卡车  如果我们能得到那个DNA...
Stop that truck.
If we can get that DNA...
麦克 你在哪里？
- Mac, where are you?
带她一起去  是的
- Take her with you.
Yeah.
我只是让他认为他是负责人
I'm just letting him
think he's in charge.
嘿 拉马克
Hey, Lammark.
吃药吧  忽略小丑
Take your pills.
Ignore the clowns.
与豺狼战斗
Fight the jackals.
离开这里
Get out of here.
每天四次在整栋大楼内进行收集
Whole building
takes a shit four times a day.
一切都混合在一起 堆放在卡车里
Everything gets mixed together,
compressed in the trucks
然后掉在这里
and then dropped here.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你们 先生们
Thank you, gentlemen.
谢谢
Thanks.
我们正在寻找一件绿色衬衫
We're looking for a green shirt
有人掉进了二楼的洗手间
someone dropped
in the second-floor restroom.
有什么建议吗？  是的
- Any tips?
- Yeah.
不要吃寿司
Don't eat the sushi.
是不是 呃 有机的东西
Isn't the, uh, organic stuff
不应该与回收分开吗？
supposed to get separated
from recycling?
是的 但我们还没有这样做
Yeah, but we don't do that yet.
我猜他们还在告诉人们把垃圾分开
I guess they're still telling
people to separate their trash
提高认识什么的
to raise awareness
or something.
谁知道？  是的
- Who knows?
- Right.
谢啦   是的 不要提它
- Thanks, man.
- Yeah, don't mention it.
美国历史上最大的袭击之一
One of the biggest
attacks in American history,
而我们所能提供的只是“请留在室内”？
and all we can offer is
"please stay indoors"?
内森 不到 72 小时
Nathan, it's been
less than 72 hours
自第一次枪击事件以来
since the first shooting.
人们已经认为你失去了控制
And people already think
you lost control.
我们需要一个改变游戏规则的人
We need a game changer.
这可能是它   不不不
- This could be it.
- No, no, no.
我们仍然没有脸
We still don't have a face.
让我们展示一下他的移动方式
Let's show the way he moves.
两百五十万观众
Two and a half million viewers.
一定有人认识这个人
Someone's got to know this guy.
基特里奇是个白痴  白痴是不可预测的
Kittridge is an idiot.
Idiots are unpredictable.
这是他妈的潘多拉魔盒
It's Pandora's fucking box.
我们冒着释放我们甚至没有的问题的风险
We risk unleashing problems
we don't even have.
我宁愿去他妈的冒险
I'd rather take a fucking risk
而不是人们认为我们一无所有
than have people think
we have nothing.
我指的是对民众的风险
I mean the risk
to the population,
而不是对政府的风险
not your administration.
那是一条线索
That's a lead.
头发 汗水
Hair, sweat.
脚印呢？
What about prints?
在大多数面料上 这不太可能 但让我的团队完成他们的工作
On most fabrics, it's unlikely,
but let my team do their job.
听着 我认为你没有在听 拉马克
Look, I don't think
you're listening, Lammark.
决定权在你手中
The decision's
out of your hands.
如果你不合作 调查也会如此
You don't play along,
so is this investigation.
这看起来不太好
This doesn't look very good.
不 它没有  完全没有  -当心
- No, it doesn't. At all.
- KITTRIDGE [on TV]: Beware.
警告 你即将看到的独家镜头
The exclusive footage
you are about to see
包含极其令人不安的图像
contains extremely
disturbing images.
如果您有孩子或对暴力敏感
If you're with kids
or sensitive to violence,
那么现在请把目光移开
then please look away now.
这些行为令人毛骨悚然
These acts are horrifying,
但它们不是怪物的产物
but they're not
the product of a monster.
他们是男人的产物
They're the product of a man.
一个危险的人 当然 但也受到了伤害
A dangerous man, sure,
but damaged, too.
这就是为什么我提出这个请求
That's why I make this plea.
如果你认识这个人 如果你喜欢这个人
If you know this man,
if you love this man,
如果你是这个人 请拨打这个号码
if you are this man,
then call this number.
嗯...  我们是来帮忙的
Well...
- We're here to help.
...最糟糕的想法获得了诺贝尔奖
...there's the Nobel
for the worst fucking idea.
团队合作使梦想成真
Teamwork makes the dream work.
哦 滚开 弗兰克
Oh, fuck off, Frank.
现在 今晚和我在一起的是玛莎·库里 教授……
Now, with me tonight
is Martha Curry, professor...
二战时期的半自动手枪
HDM, World War II era.
OSS手枪的最爱
OSS pistol of choice.
在特种部队库存之外很难找到
Hard to find outside
Special Forces inventories.
说到精神障碍
CURRY [on TV]: When it comes
to mental disorders,
暴力通常是反应性的
violence is
more commonly reactive
比计划更被动 被激怒..
than planned, triggered by...
好吧 我不得不打断你
Okay, I got to stop you there.
我们有一个电话  你好
We have a caller. Hello.
我害怕我的丈夫
WOMAN [on TV]:
I'm scared of my husband.
他最近的行为很奇怪  他是...
He's been acting weird lately.
He's...
这个男人像你的丈夫吗？
Does this man
look like your husband?
这会是他吗？
Could this be him?
其实不是 但是...
Actually not, but still...
好吧 好吧  我很抱歉  我们不提供婚姻援助
Okay, okay. I'm sorry.
This isn't marriage guidance.
我们来这里是为了查明一个大屠杀凶手
We are here to identify
a mass murderer.
好的  过去 50 年的阿森纳门将
All right. Arsenal keepers
from the last 50 years.
绿色表示可靠的不在场证明 蓝色还有待确认
Green means solid alibi,
blue still TBC.
我们的目标是粉红色的
We're targeting
the ones in pink.
他们已被部队退伍
They've been discharged
from the Forces.
黄色呢？
And the yellow?
哦 他们死了  相当可靠的不在场证明
Oh, they're dead.
Pretty solid alibi.
是的 我想我们可以放心地假设
Yeah, I think
we can safely assume
枪手就在活人中间
that the shooter
is amongst the living.
这么旧的弹药可能是遗产 长官
Munitions this old could be
quite the inheritance, sir.
这是一个非常好的观点
That's a damn good point.
很好的一点
Damn good point.
好的  商场足迹分析
Okay. Mall footprint analysis.
六年前的 CAT 工装靴
Cat work boots, six years old.
他不是第一个所有者
He's not the first owner.
左侧磨损的鞋底 有利于右侧
Soles worn on the left.
He favors the right.
还有锯末、木屑和油漆痕迹
Also sawdust, wood chips
and paint traces.
我知道去年谁杀了 1000 人
MAN [on TV]: I know who killed
a thousand people last year.
警察做到了  先生 24名军官
- The police did.
Sir, 24 officers
刚死在那个商场里
just died in that mall.
警察冒着生命危险保护你
The police risk their lives
to protect you.
...丹特赖特、安德烈希尔、布伦娜泰勒
...Daunte Wright,
Andre Hill, Breonna Taylor.
我应该继续吗？
Should I go on?
我们希望在这里创造电视历史
We are looking to
make television history here.
这个数字是独家...
This number is exclusively...
“不可杀人 ”
"Thou shalt not kill."
我在学校教室里看到的
I saw that in a school room.
你上一次看到“不可杀人”是什么时候？
When have you last seen
"Thou shalt not kill"?
你最后一次看到那个是什么时候？
When have you last seen that?
我今天的目标是试着让事情平静下来
My goal here today is to try
to calm things down,
不要让事情变得更糟
not make things worse.
因为  因为......
- MAN [on TV]:
- Because-because... ]
尝试进行对话
Try to have a dialogue.
先生 你提出了一个愚蠢的说法......
Sir, you came up
with a dumb statement...
......那来自你有偏见的内心
...that came from
your prejudiced heart.
瑞典是由维京人建立的
Sweden was founded by Vikings.
衬衫结果刚刚好
Shirt results just in.
嗯嗯？  好的
Mm-hmm?
- All right.
没有指纹 但科迪斯发现了头发和皮肤颗粒
No fingerprints, but CODIS
found hair and skin particles.
头发的末端很脆
Hair's brittle near the ends,
当它脱落时 皮肤碎片也会脱落
and when it falls out,
so do fragments of the skin.
他们想做什么？ 卖给我去屑洗发水？
What are they trying to do?
Sell me dandruff shampoo?
不 这在人群中很常见
No, it's common among people
谁遭受了严重的头部创伤
who suffered
severe head trauma.
大多数最近的枪击事件
The majority
of the last shootings
都与这些孩子有关
have all been involved
with these kids.
你在“基特里奇秀”上直播
And you are live on
"The Kittridge Show."
不要害羞
Don't be shy.
我不害羞  我很自豪
I'm not shy. I'm proud.
自豪？ 什么？
Proud? Of what?
为我的人民感到骄傲
Proud of my people.
为我们的军人感到骄傲
Proud of our soldier.
哦 他们是军队吗？
Oh, you're an army?
你在指挥这些家伙吗？
Are you commanding these guys?
你想要什么 便宜的运动鞋？
What do you want,
cheaper sneakers?
我们正在追踪他   因为他们还没有被释放..
They're on it.
They're tracking him down.
因为没有多少重要的战斗
'Cause not many great battles
在商场里战斗
were fought in a mall.
这不是游戏
This isn't a game.
这是一个重置
It's a reset.
我们国家的承诺恢复了
- Our nation's promise restored.
他使用预付费 AT 线路
He used a prepaid AT line
并拨打了 ♪67 以隐藏他的号码
and dialed star 67
to hide his number.
好的   这样可行？
Okay.
- That works?
我怎么知道你不是
How do I know you're not
只是一些有语音失真应用程序的孩子
just some kid
with a voice distortion app,
对着纳粹标志自慰？ -
jerking off on
a swastika flag? -
一把HDM手枪？ 英格拉姆 MAC-10机枪？
An HDM? An Ingram MAC-10?
那些不是孩子的玩具
Those are not kids' toys.
你可以在你的象牙城堡里嘲笑我
You can mock me
from your ivory castle,
但是你的时间也快到了 我的朋友
but your time is coming,
too, my friend.
哇哦
Whoa.
手机是在沃尔玛买的
Phone was bought at Walmart
25 分钟前在蒙哥马利县
in Montgomery County
25 minutes ago.
我在发抖
I'm shaking in my shoes.
你知道的 我希望你足够笨
You know, I hope
you're dumb enough
来找我
to come after me.
我想你会找到我的城堡
I think you'll find my castle
非常安全
- is pretty well secured.
你女儿的大学房间不是
Your
daughter's college room isn't.
现金支付 没有信用卡信息
Paid in cash,
no credit card info.
3亿美国人
300 million Americans.
4亿支枪
400 million guns.
我相信有人会愿意伸出援手
And I'm sure someone out there
would love to lend a hand.
这足以让你入狱
That's enough
to get you in jail.
最糟糕的想法 确实如此
Worst fucking idea, indeed.
你知道他们会找到你的 对吧？
You know
they'll find you, right?
只是时间问题
Only a matter of time.
不确定
Not sure about that.
这个国家有一半的罪行永远得不到解决
Half the crimes in this country
never get solved.
你的税金去了
- Your tax dollars go
致国防承包商...
to defense contractors--
无人机、导弹、核武器...  什么？
- drones, missiles, nukes...
- What?
什么？
What?
......但那些不能保护你免受我们的伤害
...but those can't
protect you from us.
所以你不喜欢我们？
So you don't like our?
我姐姐怀孕了
My sister's pregnant.
天哪 麦克   我-我很抱歉 大家
- Jesus, Mac.
- I'm-I'm sorry, everybody.
真正的敌人就在我们中间
The real enemy lies within.
夺走我们的工作 夺走我们的土地
Taking our jobs,
taking our land,
带着我们的女人
taking our women.
当他们在海外消灭你的时候
While they're overseaswiping ou,
我们可以处理所有的黑人和黄种人
we can handle
all the Blacks and yellows
以及喜欢黑鬼、渴望金钱的犹太人
and the nigger-loving,
money-hungry Jews as well.
他妈的有病   如果我们所谓的领导人
- Fucking sick.
- If our so-called leaders
不会为我们说话
won't speak up for us,
我们的步枪会
- our rifles will.
他们找到了收银机
They've located the register,
他们正在通过安全提要进行修补
and they're patching through
the security feed.
好吧 听着如果你是王牌
Okay, look, if you ace
在这些攻击背后 我要代表
behind these attacks,
I'm gonna speak on behalf
你摧毁的家庭
of the families
you've destroyed.
你是个胆小鬼
You're a coward.
你是一个黑客 一个寻求关注的人
You're a hack,
an attention seeker.
隐形军队准备战斗
The invisible
army is ready to fight.
不要自杀 孩子们
Don't kill yourselves, boys.
你的痛苦不是弱点
Your pain's not a weakness.
它是一种武器
It's a weapon.
是时候使用它了
- Time to use it.
你好？
Hello?
好吧 他们抓住了他
Okay, they got him.
电话会议于​​晚上 8 点 21 分在萨默塞特开始
The call began
at 8:21 in Somerset,
并于晚上 8 点 29 分位于西南方向 5 英里处 结束
ended at 8:29
five miles southwest.
一分钟后 芯片坏了
A minute later,
the chip went dead,
但手机的 GPS 与雪佛兰 西尔维拉多相匹配
but the phone's GPS matches
that of a Chevy Silverado,
车牌雪佛兰索维拉多的那辆 车牌阿尔法 利马 X光
license plate
Alpha, Lima, Xray,
八 零 八
eight, zero, eight.
注册到大卫·李·希克斯
Registered to
a David Lee Hicks.
他是 NRA 成员 也是 AR-15 的合法拥有者
He's an NRA member
and a legal owner of an AR-15,
一把 AK-47 和一堆猎枪
an AK-47
and a bunch of hunting rifles.
他也是“三个中心”地方分会的成员
He's also a member of the local
branch of Three Percenters.
他讨厌政府、自由主义者和犹太人
He hates government,
liberals and Jews.
我是萨默塞特指挥官
COMMANDER [over radio]:
This is Somerset commander.
我们有一辆通讯车和战术装备
We got a comms van
and tactical gear
在停机坪上为您准备就绪
ready for you on the tarmac.
请告知预计到达时间
Please advise ETA.
什么事 埃莉诺？
What is it, Eleanor?
全国步枪协会？ 百分之三？
The NRA? The Three Percent?
我们的家伙是独来独往的人 他不善于交际
Our guy's a loner,
not a joiner.
好的
Okay.
您的异议已得到妥善记录
Your objection is duly noted.
执行任务的人不会停下来吃沙拉三明治
A man on a mission
does not stop for falafel.
这不是我们的杀手  这不是我们的情况
This is not our killer.
This isn't our case.
让别人来处理吧
Let someone else
take care of it.
我不能  我正在执行命令
I can't. I'm following orders.
即使你知道他们错了？
Even when you know
they're wrong?
权力在应得的人之间存在争议
Power is disputed
between people who deserve it
和喜欢它的人
and people who adore it.
这是一场永恒的战斗
It's a perpetual fight.
我不能说我们赢了
I can't say we're winning.
现在 我们必须继续战斗
Right now,
we got to stay in the ring.
先生 恕我直言...
Sir, with all due respect...
哦 该死的 埃莉诺！ 你也在服从命令！
Oh, goddamn it, Eleanor!
You're following orders, too!
他们正在往下走
COMMANDER [over radio]:
They're heading down
威斯康星大道 17 号车
Wisconsin Avenue, car 17.
在友谊高地拦截
Intercept
at Friendship Heights.
收到
Copy that.
天啊 真他妈的冷
Jesus, it's fucking cold.
好的
Okay.
好的  畜栏
O.K. Corral.
你拥有那个白痴 伙计
You owned that moron, man.
该死的在这之后下降了
Shit's going down after this.
伙计们 现在他感谢警察保护了他的孩子
Guys, now he's thanking the
cops for protecting his kid.
这些该死的家伙...从不冒险
These fucking guys--
never risk anything,
他们认为世界围绕着他们旋转
and they think the world
spins around them.
对 因为当你在电视上时
Right, 'cause when
you're on TV,
所有的猪都跑来了
all the pigs come running.
但是谁他妈的在保护我们的孩子？ 嗯？
But who the fuck's
protecting our kids? Huh?
谁他妈的在保护我们的孩子？
Who the fuck's
protecting our kids?
我们在保护我们的孩子 你这个白痴
We're protecting our kids,
you moron.
好吧 我饿死了
Well, I'm starving.
整个警察部队保护宿舍
Whole police force
shielding a dorm room
而尸体堆积在街上
while bodies pile up
in the streets.
他不知道他会发生什么
He doesn't know
what's coming to him.
“隐形军队”正在流行
"Invisible army" is trending.
伙计们 这是一个改变游戏规则的人
This is a game changer, guys.
有些事情必须发生
Something has to happen.
好的 那么洗发水？
Okay, so shampoo?
是的 还有牙齿美白剂
Yes, and some Whitestrips.
是的   请
-  Yeah.
- Please.
好的   哦 糖果！
- Okay.
- Oh, candy!
我知道谁付钱
- I know who's paying.
他妈的淡啤酒 淡啤酒
Fucking light beer, light b,
淡啤酒 淡啤酒
light beer, light beer.
谁拥有这个地方 摩门教徒？
Who owns this place,
the Mormons?
嘘
Shh.
我会帮你拿的
I'll take that for you.
我们去他妈的酒吧吧
Let's go to a fucking bar.
啊 你会喝醉开始炫耀的
Ah, you'll get drunk
and start showing off.
我宁愿远离麻烦
I prefer to stay out
of trouble.
我在车里等你好吗 亲爱的？
I'll meet you in the car?
嗯 你给你爸爸买药了吗？
Um, did you get
the pills for your dad?
我马上回来   嗯嗯
- I'll be right back.
- Mm-hmm.
先生？
Sir?
你好
Hi.
那是什么？  嗯 这是...你能...
- What's that?
- Um, it's... Can you...
不是你的夜晚 是吗？
Not your night, huh?
先生 你能跟我一起去吗？
Sir, can you come with me, please?
说吧 姑娘  我听不见你
Speak up, girl.
I can't hear you.
就-就这样跟我来 先生
Just-just come
with me this way, sir.
我-这是一项调查吗？-不 不 不
I-Is this a survey?-No, no, no.
嗯 我只是……我们……
Um, I just... We...
你能……你能不能快点跟我来好吗？
Can you... Can you come with me
really quickly, please?
好吧 我很着急
Well, I'm in a rush.
我必须回家  我的-我的妻子...
I have to go home.
My-my wife...
是的 就是...就是这样……没关系
Yeah, that's-that's all...
That's okay.
好的 可以  -我妻子病了 我很着急
That's okay. -M-My wife
is sick, and I'm in a rush.
是的 我-我只需要你和我一起去
Yeah, I-I just
need you to come with me.
我 我真的不能   -先生 我需要
I-I really can't. -Sir, I need .
我真的没有那么多时间  -先生 现在跟我来！
I really don't have that much
time. -Sir, come with me now!
我的妻子……我的-我的妻子在等我  -现在！
My wife... my-my wife
is waiting for me. -Now!
联邦调查局！  放下你的武器！
- FBI!
- Drop your weapon!
去你的！
Fuck you!
现在放下！
Drop it now!
算了吧！
Drop it!
法尔科！  我们很好！
- Falco!
- We're good!
哦 我的天哪
ELEANOR [panting]:
Oh, my God.
联邦调查局！
FBI!
眼睛看着我！
Eyes on me!
他妈的
Fuck.
他妈的！  我需要你放下武器
- Fuck!
- I need you to drop the weapon
并让我看看那些手
and show me those hands.
你他妈的黑鬼！  我不需要这样
- You fucking nigger!
- I don't need that.
我需要你放下武器 举起手来
I need you to drop the weapon
and get those hands up.
滚出去！
Get the fuck out of here!
滚出这个地方！
Get the fuck out of this place!
放下你的武器 让我看看你的手
Drop your weapon
and show me your hands.
我要把你他妈的脑袋炸掉
I'm gonna blow
your fucking brains out.
戴维 放下武器 举起手来！
David, drop the weapon
and get those hands up!
没有黑鬼会...
- No nigger's gonna...
最后一次 滚蛋吧
For the last time,
just fuck off.
嘿 他妈的别这么跟我说话
Hey, don't fucking
talk to me like that.
我需要知道你做了什么
I need to know what you did,
我需要知道谁参与其中 我需要知道...
I need to know who's involved,
and I need to know...
他基本上是在说这是一个错误的恶作剧
He's basically saying
it's a prank gone wrong.
特蕾西证实了这一点
Tracey confirmed it.
军队不是隐形的  它根本不存在
The army's not invisible.
It just doesn't exist at all.
没有组织 没有交流
There's no organization,
no communications.
你他妈的告诉我们一些事情...
You fucking tell us something...
只是一些复制和粘贴
Just some copy-and-paste
Facebook 页面上的阴谋废话
conspiracy bullshit
on a Facebook page
有 23 个赞
with 23 likes.
那个给基特里奇的电话
And that call to Kittridge
造成了严重的附带损害
caused serious
collateral damage.
朗马克先生 你下令了吗
Mr. Lammark,
did you give the order
与“基特里奇秀”分享商场​​镜头？
to share the mall footage
with "The Kittridge Show"?
这不是我的策略
It was not my strategy.
我建议该计划有风险且有缺陷
I advised that the plan
was risky and flawed.
但这是你的调查？
But this was
your investigation?
你有全面的控制权？  是的
- You had overall control?
-  Yes.
是不是也听从你的指挥
Was it also under your command
that the public
被鼓励打电话给英威索？
were encouraged to call inwitho?
是的女士
Yes, ma'am.
演出结束仅半小时后
Just a half hour
after the show ended,
两名少年开枪打死两人
two teenagers shot
two people dead
在自杀前又伤了三人
and wounded three more
before taking their own lives.
在波士顿 燃烧瓶被扔了
In Boston,
a Molotov cocktail was thrown
透过以色列圣殿的窗户
through the window
of Temple Israel,
造成看门人改变生活的伤害
causing the janitor
life-changing injuries.
你愿意为这些罪行承担责任吗？
Do you accept responsibility
for these crimes?
我们都知道这里发生了什么
We all know
what's going on here.
这与年轻人的死亡无关
This is not about
the deaths of young men.
这是关于旧人的野心
This is about the ambitions
of old ones.
你知道凶手的名字吗？
Do you know the name
of the killer?
我知道他显然是一个远离电网的人……
I know he's someone who's lived
off the grid for obviously...
朗马克先生 请回答问题
Mr. Lammark,
please answer the question.
你知道他的职业吗？ 他的住处？
Do you know his profession?
His place of residence?
还没有
Not yet.
看来 在你的指挥下
It seems that,
under your command,
信息并不能治愈无知
information is no cure
for ignorance.
也许如果你更关注人
Perhaps if you'd paid
more attention to people
谁有资格提供帮助
who were qualified to help.
这份内部报告表明
This internal report
suggests that
你一直在接受警察的领导
you've been taking your lead
from a police officer
没有调查经验
with no investigative experience,
被局拒绝
rejected by the Bureau,
有长期的成瘾记录
with a long and proven
record of addiction.
我对吗？
Am I right?
好吧 那不是我从她的申请中得到的
Well, that's not what
I took from her application.
我看到了一个非常诚实、积极进取的人
I saw a fiercely honest,
highly motivated person.
当其他人都在帮助居民时
While everyone else
was helping residents
逃离燃烧的建筑物 法尔科警官是唯一的人
flee a burning building,
Officer Falco was the only one
冷静地拍摄他们这样做的过程
with the presence of mind
to film them doing it.
如果我们的肇事者在那些离开的人中
Had our perpetrator been
amongst those exiting,
这完全取决于她
it would've been solely
down to her.
见才识才  这是我工作的关键部分
I know talent when I see it.
It's a pivotal part of my job.
也许 拉马克先生 我们应该考虑
Perhaps, Mr. Lammark,
we should consider
你是否追求新的人才
whether your pursuit
of new talent
是因为你知道你自己失败了
is because you know
your own is failing.
你一直是一个优秀的公务员
You've been
a fine public servant,
你勇敢地与疾病作斗争 但是......
and you've fought your illness
with courage, but...
好的 好的 好的
Okay, okay, okay.
我认识这个人
I know this man.
我知道怎么找到他
I know how to find him.
你可以解雇我
You can fire me.
你得到你的牺牲
You get your sacrifice.
你留下我 你会得到你的杀手
You keep me,
you will get your killer.
你想要什么？
What do you want?
♪ 黑狗和黑乌鸦... ♪
♪ Black dogs
and black crows... ♪
它无处不在
It's everywhere.
这是什么 45分钟？
What's it been, 45 minutes?
他们准备好了新闻稿
They had
the press release ready.
“有缺陷的人 ”
"Lammarked man."
“朗马克 会尿自己的裤子
"Lammark could piss
his own pants,
还不知道是谁干的 ”
still not find out who did it."
-“朗马克...” 听着 不要读那些乱七八糟的东西
-"Lammark..."
- Listen, don't read that mess.
混蛋被评论吸引 就像苍蝇被该死的吸引一样
Assholes are attracted to
comments like flies to shit.
是的
Yeah.
谁？
Who?
什么？
What?
快点
Come on.
这是莫拉莱斯
- It's Morales.
我要在早上 7点 报到
I'm to report at 7:00 a.m.,
他正在要求您提供密码
and he's requesting
your passwords.
士气
Morales.
他很好
He's good.
我们很努力
We tried hard.
但是我们一无所获
But we got nothing.
先生 嗯...
Sir, um...
埃莉诺
Eleanor.
他们把你当作绳索
They used you as the rope.
你不是刽子手
- You're not the hangman.
好的
All right.
妈的
Oh, shit.
该回家了
- Time to go home.
哦  很高兴看到你接受得这么好
Oh. Good to see you
taking it so well.
快点  不要在孩子们面前
Come on.
Not in front of the kids.
是的  唔？
Yeah.
Hmm?
我得付钱
I got to pay.
不不不  这是在他们身上
No, no, no. This is on them.
谢谢你的饮料 伙计们
Thanks for the drinks, guys.
你说对了？  是啊 是啊
- You got it?
- Yeah, yeah.
好的
Okay.
30 年的服务  难以置信
30 years of service.
Un-fucking-believable.
♪ 我看着她从我身边走开 ♪
♪ I watch her
walk away from me ♪
♪穿过田野
- ♪ Through the fields
♪ 还有傍晚的树木
♪ And the evening trees
♪ 流向大海的河流... ♪
♪ By the river
that runs to the sea... ♪
我来了
- I'm coming.
他妈的是什么...
What the fuck is...
你知道我想不通的是什么
You know what
I couldn't wrap my head around
这就是你如何能同时出现在两个地方
is how you could be
in two places at once.
然后它就撞到了我
And then it hit me.
你在外包
You're outsourcing.
给我那个
Give me that.
嘿嘿 小心点
Hey, hey, be careful.
你粉刷了客厅
You painted the living room
3 月 12 日与来自豪华的人一起
with the guys from DeLuxe
on March 12th.
然后 在接下来的两天里
And then,
for the next two days,
你把钥匙给了别人来完成卧室
you gave the keys to someone
else to finish the bedrooms.
这就是你为紫外工作腾出时间的方式
That's how you made time
for the Ultraviolet job
3月13日和3月14日
on March 13th and March 14th.
所以我的问题是：
So my question is:
你他妈的给了谁？
Who the fuck
did you give them to?
我是这里的嫌疑人吗？
What am I, a suspect here?
因为我想我现在需要给我他妈的律师打电话
'Cause I think I need to call
my fucking lawyer right now.
不 你... -告诉她他妈的真相！
No, you... -Just tell her
the fucking truth!
很抱歉这么早叫醒你
Sorry to wake you so early.
我只是... 我想你会想抢先一步
I just... I figured
you'd want a head start.
我开始监控他的通讯 并建立了联系
I started monitoring his comms,
and I made the connection.
戴斯蒙德 宝贝
Desmond, the baby,
一直以来都是一种分散注意力的技巧
was a distraction technique
all along.
好吧 我一直在玩系统
Okay, I've been
gaming the system.
从事的工作超出了我的承受能力
Taking more jobs than
I can handle.
召集其他人...亚美尼亚人、墨西哥人、波兰人
Calling in other guys--
Armenians, Mexicans, Poles.
你的机会非常均等
Very equal-opportunity of you.
好吧 每个人都得到了公平的待遇
Well, everybody got
their fair cut.
有了这些新规定和该死的
And with these
new regulations and shit,
即使他们变得昂贵
even they got expensive.
直到我找到这个列表
Till I found this list.
有前科的人 有记录的人
Ex-cons, guys with a record
没有人会雇用
- nobody would hire.
滚出去！
Get the fuck out of here!
狗！ 快点！
The dog! Come on!
他妈的狗
Fucking dog.
这些人 他们几乎不劳而获
These guys,
they work for next to nothing,
只要你不问他们太多问题
as long as you don't ask 'em
too many questions.
相信我 无论如何你都不想和这些人聊天
And believe me, you don't want
to chat with these guys anyway.
我总是会带来午餐  好吧 这样他们就可以
I would always bring in lunch.
All right, that way, they could
工作一整天  嗯嗯
- work through the day.
Mm-hmm.
还有一个人 非常特别
And there's this one guy,
real particular.
没有肉 没有奶制品
No meat, no dairy.
就像某种该死的他妈的和尚
Like some kind
of goddamn fucking monk.
所以 有一天 我问他：“为什么？”
So, one day, I ask him: "Why?"
他说他曾经在下州的一家屠宰场工作
He says he used to work
in a slaughterhouse downstate.
之后 再也不能吃肉了
After that,
never could eat meat again.
我只知道他是迪恩
I only knew him as Dean.
高个子 总是戴着帽子
Tall guy, always wearing a cap.
是他
It's him.
他停止回答
He stopped answering.
我不再打电话了
I stopped calling.
电话是一个燃烧器  它已经死了几个月了
Phone's a burner.
It's been dead for months.
下州只有三个屠宰场
There's only three
slaughterhouses downstate.
看 我被吓到了
Look, I was scared.
我不想被捕
I didn't want to get arrested.
我害怕这家伙会来找我
I was scared this guy
would come after me.
我有一个他妈的家庭
I got a fucking family.
他回来了
He's out back.
我可以问你们一些问题吗？ -好的
Can I ask you guys
some questions? -Okay.
嗯 这个人你是不是很眼熟？
Um, does this man
look familiar to you?
打扰一下  先生们
Excuse me. Gentlemen.
我只是想占用你一点时间 谢谢
I'd just like a moment
of your time, please.
我在联邦调查局
I'm with the FBI.
这个人被通缉
This guy is wanted
in connection
与多个 多个凶杀案
with a multiple,
multiple homicide.
我想知道你们中是否有人
I'm wondering
if any of you guys
可能以前见过他
might have seen him before.
看一看  他大概十年前或更久以前来过这里
Take a look. He was here
probably a decade ago or more.
或许？ 不？
Maybe? No?
也许还在这里工作
Maybe works here still.
不
No.
但我直到 2014 年才开始在这里
But I didn't start here
till 2014.
你们需要和...谈谈
You guys need to talk to...
嘿 雷蒙娜！
Hey, Ramona!
蕾蒙娜 过来
Ramona, come over here.
这人似曾相识？
This guy look familiar?
熟悉的？ 那是迪恩他妈的波西
Familiar?
That's Dean fucking Possey.
一直低着头  没事
Kept his head down. No trouble.
不喜欢社交
Didn't like to socialize.
但是阿隆索 当年的主管
But Alonso,
the supervisor back then,
他总是在取笑迪恩
he was always teasing Dean.
叫他卡西莫多
Called him Quasimodo
因为他的头有一个令人毛骨悚然的形状
'cause his head had
a creepy shape.
可恶 愚蠢的该死的
Nasty, stupid shit.
然后一天晚上 回到 98 年左右
And then one night,
back around '98,
他们分享了汉堡行业的最后转变
they share the last shift
on the hamburger sector.
第二天早上我们进去了 阿隆索已经筋疲力尽了
We get in the next morning,
and Alonso's all ground up
在八分之三英寸处
at three eighths of an inch.
迪安说他绊倒了 掉进去了
Dean said he trippedand fell in.
我们都知道是他
we all knew it was him.
实际上 他去了罐头
He went to the can for it, actually,
但两年后他就出局了
but he was out after two years.
该案于 99 年 12 月重新开庭
The case was
reopened in December '99.
他获得了支持信的假释
He was paroled
with support letters
来自利奥波德·斯坦珀
上校和 本杰明·图斯克将军
from Colonel Leopold Stamper
and General Benjamin Tusk.
两人都曾为 波西的父亲服务
Both men served
with Possey's father,
亚瑟·朱尔斯·波西中士
Sergeant Arthur Jules Possey,
他是第 75 游骑兵团的射击教练
who was a shooting instructor
for the 75th Rangers.
当他卸任教官时
When he stepped down
as instructor,
在 2003 年去世之前 他一直是阿森纳的管理员
he remained the arsenal keeper
until he passed away in 2003.
监狱精神病医生写道
The prison psychiatrist wrote,
”尴尬的青年 垂头丧气的目光
"Awkward young man,
downcast gaze.
童年头部外伤：枪击 ”
Childhood head trauma:
gunshots."
三个月后
Three months later,
“对声音和光线极其敏感
"Extremely sensitive
to sound and light.
“睡不着
"Unable to sleep.
“宁愿对普通民众进行单独监禁
"Prefers solitary confinement
to general population.
申请永久转移  拒绝了 ”
Applies for permanent transfer.
Denied."
没有信用卡 没有家庭住址
No credit card,
no home address,
没有社保
no Social Security.
他是一个幽灵
He's a ghost.
您已到达目的地
You have
reached your destination.
我们必须打电话给麦克
We have to call Mac.
还没有
Not yet.
呼叫 Mac 就是呼叫局
Calling Mac
is calling the Bureau.
他们发送战术
They send tactical,
他们吹掉那里等等的任何铅
they blow whatever lead
is waiting in there.
如果他在里面怎么办？
What if he's in there?
然后我们给了他一个额外的时间来逃跑
Then we're giving him
an extra hour to escape.
他是一名训练有素的杀手 拥有大量武器
He's a trained killer
with a stockpile of weapons.
我现在正在给 Mac 打电话
I am calling Mac right now.
把我们都从案件中抹去？
And erase us both
from the case?
就在我们破解它的时候？
Just when we've cracked it?
不 埃莉诺  他们把我当狗一样对待
No, Eleanor.
They put me down like a dog.
现在 我要抬着那个人的头
Now, I'm gonna carry
that guy's head
直接进入J. 埃德加·胡佛大楼
right into
the J. Edgar Hoover Building
并写一本关于它的畅销书
and write a bestseller
about it.
猜猜谁是主角
Guess who's the protagonist.
他妈的！
-  Fuck!
不 冷静下来
No. Cool down.
他妈的
Fuck.
晚上好 波西夫人
Good evening, Mrs. Possey.
你知道我是谁？
You know who I am?
我知道那些盘子是什么意思
I know what those plates mean.
我已经很久没有见到他了
I haven't seen him
for a long time.
对不起
Sorry.
逮捕我或离开
Arrest me or leave.
我不是在帮你杀我儿子
I'm not helping you
kill my son.
你可以帮我们活捉他
You can help us
catch him alive.
那不是别人的优先事项
That's no one else's priority.
上次他路过是...
Last time he stepped by was...
...在病毒期间
...during the virus.
每个人都锁在自己的房子里
Everybody locked
in their houses.
迪恩在自由地漫游
Dean was roaming free.
一个游牧国王
A nomad king.
我从小就没见过他这么开心
I haven't seen him so happy
since he was a child.
他还有其他地方可以躲藏吗？
Is there anywhere else
he could be hiding?
没有他做不到的地方
There's nowhere he couldn't.
他过去常待在营地 然后是公园
He used to stay in camps,
then parks.
然后他开始睡在空荡荡的房子里
Then he started sleeping
in empty houses.
我一直都知道 嗯...
I always knew that, um...
他最终会惹上麻烦 但是……
he would eventually
get into trouble, but...
我从没想过会发生这样的事情
I never expected
anything like this.
波西夫人 谁射杀了他？
Mrs. Possey, who shot him?
我们做到了
We did.
迪恩是个很棒的小孩
Dean was a great little kid.
他很有趣也很聪明
He was funny and smart.
一直想帮忙 所以亚瑟会派他去
And always wanted to help,
so Arthur would send him
到树林里去收集目标
out into the woods
to collect the targets.
那天...
That day...
他没有意识到自己还在外面
he didn't realize
he was still out there.
砰
Bang.
两颗子弹击中了他的头部
Two pellets
got him in the head.
六岁...你能想象吗？
Six years old--
can you imagine?
他被搁置了将近一年
He was laid up
for almost a year.
差点死了
Nearly died.
现在我希望他能做到
Now I wish he did.
我们从来没有原谅过对方
We never forgave each other.
我责怪他没有检查
I blamed him for not checking.
他责怪我 因为那是我的手表
He blamed me
'cause it was my watch.
我们都是对的
We were both right.
在那之后迪恩变得不一样了
Dean was never
the same after that.
仍然很聪明 但他开始讨厌上学
Still smart,
but he started hating school
和他过去喜欢的生日派对
and birthday parties,
which he used to love.
孩子们可能很残忍 你知道的
Kids can be cruel, you know.
所以你丈夫训练他自卫？
So your husband trained him
to defend himself?
不仅
Not only.
他想给他一个在军队中的未来
He wanted to give him
a future in the Army.
而且 呃...
And, uh...
迪恩很有才华
and Dean was talented.
他只是不暴力
He just wasn't violent.
不是那时
Not back then.
他喜欢透过望远镜看
He liked to look
through the scope
在昆虫和鸟类
at insects and birds.
他会拿着步枪躺在草地上几个小时
He'd spend hours lying
in the grass with his rifle
只是看着月亮
just looking at the moon.
毫不奇怪 他们拒绝了他
Not surprisingly,
they rejected him.
“不适合服务 ”
"Unfit for service."
这让亚瑟心碎
That broke Arthur's heart.
先生...
Sir...
不 不要！
No, don't!
他会开枪打死你  不要动
- He'll shoot you. Don't move.
他会杀了你
He'll kill you.
He will kill you.
你说你可以帮忙
You said you could help.
如何？
How?
如何？！
How?!
你说你可以让他活着
You said that
you could keep him alive,
所以 你可以做什么？
so what can you do?
喇叭是给他的？
The horn was for him?
是的
Yes.
这意味着他信任你   是的
- That means he trusts you.
- Yes.
这就是你要做的
Here's what you're gonna do.
来拿我的电话
Come get my phone.
拿我的枪
Get my gun.
也得到他的
Get his, too.
迪恩！
Dean!
她是来帮忙的！
- She's here to help!
她说她不参与这个案子
She says she's off the case.
没有人知道他们在这里
No one knows they're here.
我相信她 我认为你也应该相信
I believe her, and I think
that you should, too.
凭借你的病史 她可以让你免于入狱
With your medical history,
she can keep you out of jail.
你会去达洛维
You'd be going to Dalloway.
这是一个在树林里的设施
It's a facility in the woods.
我的意思是迪恩来吧
I mean, Dean, come on.
它必须停止
It's got to stop.
看看你做了什么
Look what you've done.
你必须投降
You must surrender.
儿子？
Son?
如果你不跟他们一起去...
If you won't go with them...
...跟我来
...come with me.
哦 天哪​​  哦 他妈的
ELEANOR [voice trembling]:
Oh, God. Oh, fuck.
哦 他妈的
Oh, fuck.
我一直以为我会比她先死
I always thought
I'd die before her.
听着 迪恩
L-Listen, Dean.
我的名字是埃莉诺   不
- My name is Eleanor.
- Don't.
不要那样做  不要用你的废话
Don't do that.
Don't use your bullshit
警校战术训练在我身上
police academy
tactics training on me.
我不是那个人
I'm not that guy.
我不是吸毒的疯子
I'm not some drugged-out nutjob
你可以通过同意我来拖延
you can stall
by agreeing with me
就像我们是邻居一样使用我的名字
and using my first name
like we're neighbors.
你是来杀我的 不是来借糖的
You came here to kill me,
not to borrow a cup of sugar.
所以不要告诉我你关心我
So don't tell me
you care for me,
因为我看得出你没有
'cause I can see
that you don't.
您一次无痛释放的机会
Your one chance
at a painless release
不是像其他人一样撒谎
is not to lie
like everybody else.
好吧 你错了
Well, you're wrong.
他们带我进来是因为他们认为我能理解你
They brought me in because they
thought I'd understand you.
我可以同情   最后
- That I could empathize.
- Finally.
我杀了 200 个人 然后有人在乎
I kill 200 people,
then someone gives a shit.
你有什么进展吗？
You making any progress?
好吧 我在这里
Well, I'm here.
而且我不怕死
And I'm not afraid of dying.
有时候 我恨自己 恨死我了
Sometimes I hate myself
so much that I want to die.
有时我认为这会容易得多
And sometimes I think
it'd be a lot easier
更爱自己
to love myself more
如果其他人都被炸飞了
if everyone else
was blown off the map.
但他们不会
But they won't be.
这没有什么坏处 迪恩
This doesn't hurt, Dean.
你是娱乐
You are entertainment.
你是屏幕上的时间
You're time on screen.
他们用点击来衡量你
They measure you in clicks.
他们想要更多
And they want more.
更多的行动 更多的血液
More action, more blood.
改变叙述  进监狱
Change the narrative.
Go to jail.
只要能给大家解释
Just if you can
explain to everyone
为什么这对你有意义
why it made sense to you
拿起武器开始射人……
to grab a weapon
and start shooting people...
这有什么不合理的？
What doesn't make sense
about it?
人们发出如此多的噪音
People make so much noise.
年复一年 对着一些愚蠢的烟火大喊大叫
Year after year, shouting
at some stupid fireworks,
仿佛寂静和黑暗是需要击败的敌人
as if silence and darkness
were enemies to defeat.
回到你他妈的洞穴去
Go back to your fucking caves.
晚上 有很多灯亮着
At night, there are
so many lights on
你甚至看不到星星
you can't even see the stars.
我要时间  我想要空间
I want time. I want space.
他们想要东西
They want things.
操他们
Fuck them.
你要么非常愚蠢要么非常沉睡
You've either got to be
very stupid or very asleep
发现这个游戏很有趣
to find this game entertaining.
人们擦洗
People scrubbing,
每天清理别人的屎12小时
cleaning up other people's shit
for 12 hours a day
为了一把绿纸？
for a handful of green paper?
不是我
Not me.
不再
Not anymore.
相信我 我 嗯……我知道你在说什么
Believe me, I, um... I know
what you're talking about.
我只希望我们能进行这次对话
I just wish
we'd had this conversation
在你越线之前
before you crossed the line.
我今天去了屠宰场
I went to
the slaughterhouse today.
有一个女人 拉蒙娜
There was a woman, Ramona.
她好像很喜欢你
She seemed fond of you.
是的
Yeah.
她还不错
She wasn't bad.
那个地方 虽然...
That place, though...
一天早上 在通宵之后
One morning,
after an all-nighter,
我向后追踪牛的路径
I traced the cow's path backwards.
从汉堡区开始 经过切割
Started in the burger section,
went through cutting,
看到牛被剥皮切成两半
saw the cows getting skinned
and cut in two,
然后奶牛把螺栓钉在头上
then the cows getting
the bolt to the head.
然后我跟着一辆卡车回到了农场
Then I followed a truck
back to the farm.
翻过篱笆
Jumped a fence,
绕着湖走了一圈 他们就在那里
walked around the lake,
and there they were.
华丽的
Magnificent.
他们似乎很感激他们的存在
They seemed grateful
for their existence.
他们不想改变
They didn't want to change.
不想进化
Didn't want to evolve.
他们只是想在那里呼吸
They just wanted to be there, breathing.
生与死
To live and die,
然后消散回到整体
then dissipate
back into the whole.
这不正是我们都想要的吗？
Isn't that what we all want?
你为什么不走开？
Why don't you just go away?
我确定有一个地方你可以去住
I'm sure there's a place
you can go live
就像农场里的奶牛
like the cows out on the farm.
不
Nah.
你去的任何地方都属于某个人
Everywhere you go
belongs to someone.
无论走到哪里 你都得有钱
Everywhere you go,
you got to have money.
他们...他们必须知道你是谁
They-they got to know
who you are.
他们……他们一直在检查你
They... they're always
checking up on you.
他们总是在问
They're always asking.
他们总是在看
They're always watching.
现在他们有了无人机
Now they got drones,
从外太空侦察的卫星
satellites spying
from outer space.
这整个星​​球都是他妈的监狱
This whole planet's
a fucking prison.
为什么我必须遵守你的规则？
Why do I have to play
by your rules?
我不知道如何赚钱
I don't know how to make money.
我不知道如何赢得选票
I don't know
how to win votes.
但是谁拥有真正的权力呢？
But who has the real power?
一千尺外的生死
Life and death
from a thousand feet away.
我可能找不到和平 但我可以报复
I may not find peace,
but I can deliver retribution.
报应不是你需要的
Retribution is not
what you need.
然后怎样呢？
What, then?
爱？
Love?
是的
Yes.
我们中的一些人受到如此虐待
Some of us have been
so mistreated
我们甚至不知道那是什么感觉
we don't even know whatit's lik.
他们烧毁了我们通向快乐的桥梁
They burned
our bridges to pleasure.
但我认为它们可以重建
But I think
they can be rebuilt.
不
Nah.
对我来说太晚了
Too late for me.
那列火车走了
That train's gone.
不过 我很欣赏这种努力
I appreciate the effort, though.
不用担心  没有下一个了
Don't worry. There's no next.
你还活着是有原因的
You're still alive
for a reason.
你说你要帮我 嗯 就是这样
You said you wanted to help me,
well, this is how.
我想去那边
I want to go over there.
我想躺在她身边
I want to lay down next to her.
我想像小时候一样拥抱她
I want to hug her
like when I was a kid.
你要等到我睡着了
And you're gonna wait
till I fall asleep.
我真的很累  会很快的
I'm real tired. It'll be quick.
那你就要朝我的脑袋开枪了
Then you're gonna
shoot me in the head.
我不希望我的尸体遍布新闻
I don't want my corpse
all over the news.
所以你拿着那罐汽油
So you take that can
of gasoline,
你把它倒在我们身上并点燃了我们
you pour it over us
and set us on fire.
烧烤结束后
When the barbecue's done,
你打电话给你的朋友 然后拿起你的奖杯
you call your friends
and you pick up your trophy.
那是交易吗？
That a deal?
埃莉诺？
Eleanor?
是的 迪恩
Yes, Dean.
我会仁慈而恭敬地处决你
I'd kindly and respectfully
execute you.
你以为我傻？
You think I'm stupid?
不 迪恩
No. Dean.
不  迪恩！
Don't. Dean!
停下！
Stop!
帮助！ 帮助！
Help! Help!
波西夫人 开门
Mrs. Possey, open the door.
迪恩！
Dean!
停下！ 迪恩 我没有连线
Stop! Dean, I'm not wired.
一定有人听到了枪声
Someone must have heard
the shots.
我没有线！
I'm not wired!
波西夫人 警察
Mrs. Possey, police.
迪恩 住手！
Dean, stop!
听我说！
Listen to me!
迪恩！
ELEANOR [muffled]:
Dean!
他妈的
Fuck.
开枪了！ 从棚子里开枪！
Shots fired!
Shots fired from the shed!
迪恩！
Dean!
为什么？
Why?
有些孩子因为你的矛盾而失去了他们的父亲？
Some kid just lost their father
all 'cause you're conflicted?
迪恩 你必须停下来
Dean, you have to stop.
这些人都有家庭
These people have families.
你正在给他们几十年的痛苦
You are giving them decades
of suffering
而你讨厌的一切都保持不变
while everything you hate
stays the same.
他妈的！
Fuck!
我知道你在听我说话
I know you're listening to me.
如果你不是 杀了我
Kill me if you're not.
你是那个想要停下来的人
You're the one
who wants to stop.
五分钟前你问我
Five minutes ago, you asked me
射中你的头部并烧毁你的身体
to shoot you in the head
and burn your body.
那证明你有多累
That proves how tired you are
以及所有这一切是多么不必要
and how unnecessary
all of this is.
看着我！
Look at me!
波西先生 你被包围了！
Mr. Possey, you're surrounded!
立即举起双臂离开棚子！
Get out of the shed right now
with your arms raised!
你说结束了
You said it was over.
解开我 让我来对付他们
Untie me,
and let me handle them.
你知道我会做对你最好的事情
You know I'll do
what's best for you.
波西先生
Mr. Possey,
我要你现在就离开那里
I want you to walk
out of there right now,
我希望你慢慢来 好吗？
and I want you
to do it slowly, okay?
滚出去 混蛋！
Come the fuck out, asshole!
迪恩
Dean.
留在我身边  留在我身边
Stay with me. Stay with me.
我老板的车
My boss's car.
到现在为止 他们知道我在这里
By now, they know I'm here.
如果他们知道我还活着 他们就不会开枪了
If they know I'm alive,
then they won't fire.
出来吧 混蛋！
Come out, motherfucker!
迪恩  迪恩
Dean. Dean.
留在我身边  留在我身边
Stay with me. Stay with me.
你被预订的那一刻
The minute that you get booked,
我会确保你得到你需要的帮助
I will make sure that
you get the help you need.
药物
Medication.
那该死的有效
That shit works.
你会睡得像个婴儿
You'll sleep like a baby.
当你再次睁开眼睛时 我会
And when you open
your eyes again, I will be
就在那里帮助你度过难关
right there to help you
get through this.
我要数到五
I'm gonna give you
to the count of five.
迪恩 迪恩 你不用解开我
Dean, Dean, you don't
have to untie me,
但就这样吧  留在我身边  留在我身边
but just stay like this.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
四！
Four!
请把它放下
Put that down, please.
三！
Three!
出去！  二！
- Get out!
- Two!
迪恩 放下它 否则你得自杀
Dean, put that down,
or you have to kill yourself.
一！
One!
对不起 但你必须这样做  做吧！
I'm sorry, but you have to.
Do it!
时间到了 混蛋！
Time's up, asshole!
留在原地！
- Stay right where you are!
让我看看你的手！  他妈的别动！
- Show me your hands!
- Don't fucking move!
等等 等等 等等 等等 等等！
Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait!
抓住！ 抓住！
Hold! Hold!
他还活着  埃莉诺？
He's alive.
Eleanor?
他受了伤 但他还活着
He's wounded, but he's alive.
到底发生了什么？
What the hell happened?
你为什么不给我打电话？  我试过  我真的试过了
- Why didn't you call me?
- I tried. I really tried.
什么？  拉马克不让我
- What?
- Lammark wouldn't let me.
所有单位
- OFFICER [over radio]:
- All units,.
我们需要更多实地人员
We need more men on the ground.
他们沿河而下
OFFICER [over radio]: They
traversed out to the river.
分发武器和背心  收到
- Distribute weapons and vests.
Copy that.
直升机部队 待命
OFFICER [over radio]:
Chopper unit, stand by.
警犬队 看来我们闻到了气味
Canine team, looks
like we picked up a scent.
收到  你的位置是什么？
Copy that.
What's your location?
我们在第九区 往南走
We're in sector nine,
heading south.
我们有脚印
We have footprints.
收到  重新路由所有移动单元
Copy that.
Rerouting all mobile units.
九区 厂区
Sector nine, factory site.
埃莉诺 我们听完了你的汇报
Eleanor, we went through
your debriefing,
我们想出了这个策略
and we came up
with this strategy.
集体地
Collectively.
我们希望您会乐意签字
We hope you'll be happy
to sign.
整个行动将保持机密
The entire operation
will remain classified.
就记录而言
As far as
the record's concerned,
这是一个授权计划
this was an authorized plan.
巴尔的摩警方和联邦调查局破案了…
BPD and the Bureau cracked
the case, got our killer,
在州政府的全力支持下找到了我们的凶手
with the state government's
full support.
时期
Period.
只字不提那所房子里发生的事
Not a word about
what happened in that house,
只字不提你吸毒的历史
not a word
of your history with drugs.
然而 尽管你以前的记录
However,
despite your previous record,
我们都同意你不仅证明了自己
we all agreed that you've
more than proved yourself,
所以该局想给你一个永久职位
so the Bureau would like
to offer you a permanent post
作为情报分析员
as intelligence analyst.
这是你收买我沉默的方式吗？
Is this your way
of buying my silence?
你真希望我帮忙掩饰你的无能
You really expect me
to help cover up
你缺乏良好的判断力
your incompetence,
your lack of judgment,
你愿意冒生命危险吗？
your willingness
to put lives at risk?
他正在努力帮助你 埃莉诺
He's trying
to help you, Eleanor.
你被停职了
You were suspended.
拉马克被解雇了
Lammark had been fired.
但是 你还是非法联系了郎
But still,
you illegally contacted Lang,
在没有律师的情况下审问他
interrogated him
without a lawyer
并且擅自行动
and set off
without authorization,
直接导致 17 人死亡
leading directly
to 17 extra fatalities.
所以与其让媒体让你成为十五分钟的英雄……
So, instead of letting
the press make you a hero
然后毁了你的生活
for 15 minutes,
then destroying your life,
我们正在为您提供一个未来
we're offering you
a way forward.
我要你纪念拉马克
I want you to honor Lammark
追授英勇勋章
with a posthumous
Medal of Valor.
我要你把他的全部养老金转给他丈夫
And I want you to transfer his
full pension to his husband.
我们能做到这一点
We can do that.
我不想成为分析师
I don't want to be an analyst.
让我做特工 你知道我活该
Make me special agent.
You know I deserve it.
完毕
Done.
任何欺骗 现在或以后 我会确保每个人都知道......
Any tricks, now or later,
and I will let everyone know
你的手上沾满了鲜血
that you have blood
on your hands.
谢谢 埃莉诺
Thanks, Eleanor.
我很高兴我们相互理解
I'm glad
we understand each other.
不是这样的
We don't.
干得好 法尔科
Good work, Falco.
谢谢你 先生
Thank you, sir.
如果我们抓住这个家伙
LAMMARK [voice-over]:
We get this guy,
这一切都消失了
this all goes away,
我们都可以完成我们本该完成的工作
and we can both do the job
we were meant to.